It's Friday.
The best day of the week.
Man, am I excited for this.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, everybody.
How are you doing?
It's Hamis day.
Hey, Tark.
Thanks for using your Prime subscription on me, man.
I appreciate it.
Use it to spam some Hamis, the dancing Hamis, because that's the superior Hamis.
We've got the singing bowls back.
Hopefully I set everything up right this time.
These singing bowls should not show up in the VOD.
So this is strictly for live.
This is the experience you get when watching live.
You get the singing bowls.
Usually you just arrived after a two-day trip.
Welcome.
Kick back, relax and watch me suffer.
But maybe also do something amazing today because I have big plans.
I added two.
So unfortunately, the animated emotes only you can't put them as free.
They have to be tier one or above.
So I put a non-dancing one for everyone.
So you can use that if you want.
Everyone should have access to a Hamis.
That's what I think.
Anyway, I'm going to jump right in, I think, because I am just going to play my game.
I'm way too excited about this.
I also got to turn off the singing bowls.
There we go.
No more singing bowls because now it's time for Noita.
Man, I had a crazy run last time and I discovered a bunch of shit.
I can't wait to see what other stuff I'm going to find.
That's the best part of this game.
Experimenting with all the different shit you find, the spells and all that.
Oh, it's so good.
Hold on, let me actually switch.
Let me put on my keyboard because the on-screen keyboard is just not optimal for video games.
I keep forgetting this.
Why do I always...
There we go.
I have to connect this every time I want to play a game.
Alright, let's go.
What do we have here?
We have a... wow.
Three spark bolts on that and then we have normal bombs.
Okay, so unfortunately I cannot go up there and have some fun in the beginning.
So I'm just going to head straight in.
Music starts straight away.
Very nice.
Game is a bit loud.
Let me turn that down.
There we go.
Nice.
Not my optimal one, but I'll take it.
You're shooting everything?
Today is the day we will not die.
At all.
This will be the cleanest gameplay you've ever seen.
Coming right up.
Mark my words.
I will play patient, I will play precise, and I will play smart.
Those are the three main adjectives we're going to be using today.
See that guy?
He's no longer here.
Give me that.
Dude, I can't wait to see what perks I'm going to get.
There are so many things I'm excited about.
Hey!
There we go.
The corpse was actually blocking the shot.
Incredible.
There's a vat of acid.
No, toxic sludge, sorry.
Toxic sludge.
Doesn't make it any better, does it?
Still a bunch of not good things for you.
Is that a hammis?
Hamis!
I'm sorry I have to kill you.
Oopsie daisy.
Look at all these hammises.
It's a whole family.
I just murdered everyone.
The women and the children too.
Nice.
Sweet.
That was really smooth.
Man, things are going well so far.
Man, I had the craziest ones last time.
That was such a good time.
I got really far and then I... Oh, spoiler alert if you haven't seen it of course, but...
I had a very unfortunate death after all that.
Very anticlimactic, but it was a death that also came with a lesson.
A very important one that I shall remember intensely.
Trust me.
And that lesson has to do with electricity and water and how they don't mix.
Pheromone potion.
I'll take it.
Also, what do I have?
Brine potion!
What the fuck is that?
Wait a minute.
Isn't brine salty?
Isn't that like salt water or like sea water?
What the hell?
Oh!
I can just put it down?
I didn't... Cool?
I didn't realize you could do that.
Right.
It's just salty water.
Awesome.
Briny water.
I specifically remember one sentence such as the briny air fills you or something from a certain detective game.
God, I can't even remember anything right now.
Look at all these guys.
So these guys are called...
Hurto, I think.
Doesn't this guy look like Barney from The Simpsons?
The people with the dynamite walking around?
Kind of looks like the guy who burps all the time.
Right?
Maybe I'm crazy, but just his outline sort of reminds me of that.
Okay.
Is that gold?
It's just a pile of gold here.
What the fuck?
That reminds me.
I should be using my bombs if I find a big deposit of gold.
Just extract that shit immediately.
Can I pass here?
I can't.
Oh, okay.
Is there anything over there anyway?
I don't think so.
So far, the play has been perfect.
Let's keep it up.
We have this toxic sludge monster.
Also called the TSM.
Shotgun man.
Sir, do you want some of this?
Give me that gold.
Hamis.
What is that down there?
The hell is that?
Look at that.
It's a guy with a lamp.
Oh!
Okay.
Oh, he may... All right, this is the shit.
Run!
I've died a lot to this.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is a guy to be afraid of.
Where'd he go?
Is that you?
It is.
Run!
Where's the cloud?
Man, he has HP.
Shit!
You know what?
I can bomb him.
You like that?
I hit the other guy.
But that's fine.
My God, this guy has some HP.
This is an insane enemy.
I crit.
Got him.
Very nice.
Very cool.
Let's go up here instead.
Ah!
Start from the top, and then work our way down.
That is the rule we shall follow today.
A chest!
Holy shit!
I'm so excited.
Wait, I should probably enter from the top.
Here.
That guy is going to burn alive, hopefully.
Okay, there's him.
Is this up there?
Sir, your shoulder is...
The fuck just happened?
Did the chest just burn away?
No, man!
Fuck!
Also, this guy... Wait, this guy has a wand.
Wait, was there a wand inside?
He took it?
Is that what's happening?
Motherfucker.
Bro, I can't hit him.
Ah, shit.
At least he died.
Gimme that.
What is it?
Spitterbolt with timer.
But I'll take it.
May as well take it if we don't have all the slots filled, right?
Very cool.
Let me try it.
What's with the timer?
Oh, right.
It doesn't do anything because we need something on the right for that timer to work.
No, wait.
That's a trigger.
Oh, wait.
No.
It's the same.
You can't have something that happens after a certain time if you don't have something that happens after a certain time.
Makes a lot of sense, if you think about it.
Look at all the hemispheres.
This is the hemisphere.
That guy's still alive.
There we go.
Also,
is this one?
No one, man.
No one's happening.
Okay, nevermind.
Bop, bop, bop.
Nice.
Dude, we're getting good gold.
350 gold already, baby.
This is an insane start.
And there's a wand up here.
I love it.
Grab it.
Oh, wait a minute.
Am I...
I have no bombs left!
Shit!
But wait, I have an idea.
I have an idea.
That's a trap.
Get that shit out.
Okay, you know what?
Let's do this.
Hopefully this thing won't explode.
Okay, here we go, here we go.
This is perfect.
Let me in.
Yeah, I'm a genius.
Ooh, what's happening there?
Whoa, what's happening?
Why did it look like that?
There was like a toxic sludge weather front.
And everything burns.
Oh, this is so good.
Just the way everything interacts with each other.
Frickin' amazing.
I can't believe it all works so well and seamlessly.
It's insane.
Okay, here we go.
It's a wand with a firebolt.
Okay.
Cool.
Nice.
25 shots.
And I do believe this makes a hole in the ground, so we can do a bit of digging if you want.
And there's another wand!
Oh my god, this is just amazing.
Ah, is that another trap situation?
It's definitely in some toxic sludge.
Or is this?
Yeah, toxic sludge.
So the way to get in there, probably from the top would be the best.
Ah, we have to drain this.
Let's see.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then get out of the way.
Here we go.
Drain it!
That's gonna eat through this?
No, wait, this is not acid.
This is toxic sludge.
Oh, shit.
I may need to drain it even more.
From below.
Hmm, can I get through here?
I can!
Oh, and that's even gonna burn.
That's perfect.
In fact, set fire to it.
Yes!
Dude, that was so good.
Look how good I am.
Oh!
Exquisite me!
Get out of the way.
Ah, okay, that gold can go fuck itself?
I don't want it.
Three arrows.
I like that.
I think I want it instead of this.
Hold on, let me check the want stats, actually.
No shuffle.
Only two slots.
A lot of mana, but a low mana charge speed.
Or maybe I want to replace the bomb.
The bomb is so good, though.
This is actually, it's a shit wand.
There's only one slot, right?
This is a shit wand.
I should replace it.
Yeah, fuck it.
We can probably find more bombs.
And we just took a bunch of damage.
Because I was standing on something toxic.
Hey, this is great.
Five damage, and it slices, right?
Just like my beloved glowing lance.
Uh, wait a minute.
Right.
Where do I go now?
I want to see what's up here.
Do I, though?
Toxic rock?
No, we're gonna play it safe, like I said.
Instead of going that way, let's go down first and see what's there.
Oh!
Fucking him is...
That just took a lot of my HP.
Fuck.
Aw, man.
Shit.
Yo.
There we go, headshot.
Come on.
Show yourself.
What's that watery sound?
Oh, are we at the lava?
What the fuck?
Oh.
Okay.
We can actually get through here.
If we need to.
Okay.
Don't see anything up there worth exploring.
Just be careful here.
Whoa.
There we go.
That gold is ripped.
That's fine.
Fuck off!
Oh, that was toxic.
Bad idea.
Don't kick the toxic animals.
You're there.
Come on.
There we go.
Ah, not again.
I'm actually slowly losing HP constantly here.
I need to pull myself together.
So that's a dead end.
I do kind of want to go down below, but maybe there's a way down there without having to blow it up.
Let's see.
Also, I need to put this... there.
This is my primary one now.
Primary damage dealer.
Oh yeah, it's actually pretty good.
That's decent damage.
I think it's three hits on these guys.
Nice.
Smooth operator here.
And now we're below.
Is that...
Is that a drunk hammers?
Sir!
What are you doing?
It's whiskey.
That's fucking awesome.
Hold on.
I want to try something.
What if I put...
worm pheromone into that?
Is it reacting?
What's happening?
Let me try water.
I don't think anything's happening.
If I put water into toxic sludge, it all turns to water, very rapidly.
There's a very bloody guy there.
Seems like he's seen some action.
Let's have him see some more.
Shit.
Don't mess with me.
Bow and arrow, master.
It is I.
Oh god damn, it's Friday, dude.
I felt that in my bones just now.
Felt good.
It's like a reverberation all across my body.
Reverberation of happiness.
Rotten meat.
What if I eat it?
Food poisoning.
You know, that makes a lot of sense, if you think about it.
Am I losing HP?
Yeah, don't eat rotten meat.
That's like, you know, very logical.
Also, look at my money right now.
Perfect amount of money.
Unfortunately, I gotta pick up some more money.
Okay.
Man, this area is big.
Is it usually this big?
Enemy over there?
In fact, I can blow this up, let me do that.
Blow!
Up!
Nice, gain access to everything.
What the hell is that guy doing?
I think he was trying to hit the Huerto down here.
And he failed.
So he blew himself up.
Let's wait for this to blow over.
I could probably go.
Go!
Wait, he's protected.
The fuck?
Kill him!
My god.
There we go.
Nice!
Still going pretty well.
27 HP is a little risky, though.
Not gonna lie.
But, I mean, we're at the very beginning.
You know, it's whatever.
It's okay.
There's a fucking wand again!
So many!
What have I done to deserve all this?
Let's get through here.
Oh, that was weird.
It rolls downhill.
I mean, nice!
Let's go.
Yeah!
Oh, wait a minute, is that...
Do we have a fireman?
What's happening over there?
Oh, wait, that's a trap!
Go now.
Okay.
It's a shitty wand.
Don't want it.
Someone's throwing things?
I heard you.
Oh, look at that over there!
Look how many they're fucking...
Oh, there's a heart!
Oh!
There's a guy up there.
Take care of him.
Now we're gonna snipe these and play it safe.
Go here.
Oh, wait, it's locked.
I can't get in.
That means we gotta blow it up.
Burn!
Let's get ready to shoot them.
There's a big guy in there as well.
That's actually a little risky.
Maybe I'll use my firebolt against those.
Oh, shit!
Sick.
Pretty effective, I gotta say.
Pretty effective.
Let's just wait for all this to blow over before we head in there.
I don't care about the gold.
I have enough.
Wait, what happened to the heart?
Tell me it just fell down.
Oh, it's toxic everywhere!
Oh, I'm surrounded by toxic shit!
Sick snipe though.
Nice, it's down here.
Okay.
Good to know.
Okay, I don't want to go through yet.
I'm greedy AF, okay?
I know it.
But it's a sort of safe way to be greedy that I'm doing here, because I'm playing safe.
I'm not gonna die.
Every single step I will take will be measured.
You know?
Measure twice.
Cut once.
That's my motto.
Oh!
Chest!
Fuck yeah!
What did I get?
Oh, shit!
I got a...
Oh, wait, it's one of those things!
Right!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I found one of these before.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Very nice.
So what is the deal with this?
This tiny rock looks most fiery, but when touched, only a pleasant warmth can be felt.
I kinda wanna try and sacrifice this on the altar of the gods or whatever.
So, the question is, I don't wanna go there now because there's a boss there.
So the next time I find one of those altar-looking things, I will try and place it on top of it.
Or I can try and throw it in some liquid.
Probably just gonna set it on fire, alright.
Also, look at this!
The acid burnt through most of this shit down here.
I wonder if there's anything down there.
Ah, probably not.
I think I should just go in.
I have 477 monies.
Good start!
Love it!
Let's take this.
Yoink!
We wait with the other one.
Let's see what we got.
We have...
Dropper bolt.
Okay.
Sea of lava.
Horizontal barrier, that one fucked me up once.
Spitter bolt.
Acid cloud.
Spitter bolt with timer, heavy spread.
Ooh, okay, I'm gonna try this for sure.
Let's see what this is all about.
A very heavy explosive bolt.
Okay.
25 uses, 80 mana drain, 50 damage.
How much is that compared to...
Oh, 33, okay.
Dropper bolt.
Why is it called dropper?
What does that even mean?
Let's try it.
Try it over here, I guess.
Near the water.
Oh, that's why it's called dropper bolt.
It's heavy as fuck.
Oh, it says very heavy.
I just thought it meant like more damage.
But it's actually very heavy.
Okay.
So that would make sense to put that on a trigger, no?
I don't have any...
Oh, no, I have a timer.
Shit, I don't know what to get.
I guess I can get everything.
All seeing eye.
Seems pretty dope to have.
Um, how about we try the acid cloud.
Heavy spread.
Spitter bolts.
Oh, I can use...
Oh wait, oh wait, before we do anything.
Let's see what we have here.
Fire immunity.
That's enticing.
Invisibility.
Exploding gold.
Gold dropped by enemies.
Explode when it disappears.
No, I don't want that.
Dude, both of these sound amazing.
But I had a great run with invisibility, so I feel like...
But fire immunity?
Here's the thing.
I'm pretty good at avoiding fire.
I'm not gonna say I'm the best, but...
Fire is not my main enemy here.
You know?
I'm gonna go for invisibility.
It's too good, man.
Fuck yeah.
Easy clap.
Spitter bolts.
Let me grab some fireballs.
Because I think they're pretty dope.
Now sea of lava.
So that's four...
Oh, I barely don't have enough for all three, but that's fine.
Actually, I don't want the horizontal barrier anyway.
Fuck yeah, look at this.
Okay, let's do some building.
Let's see what we got.
I like the arrows.
This has 0.20 cast delay.
0.05.
Hold on.
This would make this one pretty sick, no?
If I do this.
Bop, bop, bop.
But it has a long recharge.
That's the problem.
Let's see here.
Spitter bolt with timer.
Firebolt.
I think I definitely want a wand just with some fireballs.
Like that.
You know?
Doesn't matter that this is shuffle, it's fine.
I don't want spark bolts because I have my main...
My main damage wand is basically...
Wait a minute.
0.202.
0.17.
0.0.
Wait a minute now.
Actually, what is best here?
Overall, let me see here.
Okay, that's a bit too slow for me.
We're gonna put these down here.
That's my main damage for now.
That is my main damage wand.
And the next one is gonna be my fireball wand.
So we're gonna put this here.
The third one, I think I want the all-seeing eye on that.
Wait, what's happening?
Oh, I don't have enough mana on it.
Oh, right, okay, okay.
So put that there, I guess.
And in this one we can do something else.
The dropper bolt, maybe?
Would I like something else on that, maybe?
Maybe?
Honestly?
Let's try this.
Let's try and see what happens.
On a timer, huh?
How do I know how long that timer is?
That did nothing.
Wait, a short-lived magical bolt that casts another spell after a timer runs out.
Am I crazy?
Wait, what?
Oh, wait, it has to hit the wall?
Wait.
Huh?
Oh, wait a minute.
Uh...
80...
Ah, it's the mana.
It's the mana.
I don't have enough mana.
I see.
Shit.
Didn't I have another one with time?
Oh, they both split.
What if I do...
Nah, that's not that cool.
I mean...
Heavy spread...
Fire bolts...
Maybe I'll just go...
Oh, I can't do that either.
Fuck, that's 140.
Ah, that's crap.
So maybe I put these...
Yeah, let's change things up here.
Let's put the Sea of Lava on...
on this one.
Hold on, do I even want this?
Is this even a great idea to have?
I feel like I would kill myself with that.
But I don't know.
So I can put it here, but in this one we can put...
the...
fire bolts.
You know what, I can even do this, honestly.
Because why not, right?
This one is not gonna...
Oh!
Actually, yeah.
This is a bit chaotic though.
Because I'm gonna be expecting...
Oh, you know what, I'm gonna be using these first and then when I'm out I have this.
That's the plan.
Yeah.
We're actually... No, no, no, I'm gonna do this and that.
I wanna try the Sea of Lava just to see and if I don't like it I can use the remaining two and I will only have...
dropper bolts left.
Not bad, I like it.
Let's go with that, huh?
Bop, bop, bop.
Not bad.
Just hit the lamp.
Very cool.
Let's go, baby!
And the best part is, now that I'm a ninja, I'm invisible.
My three arrows are gonna do crazy damage.
Because I can pretty much always hit them with it.
Notice the symbol that happens in the center whenever you would leave.
It looks like a...
symbol that goes up and then it has like a little triforic up there somehow.
And I'm invisible, baby.
Bop, bop, bop.
Oh, it's so good.
Yeah!
But hold on, this is the...
Yeah, no stains.
Remember, no stains.
Stains not allowed.
That's a rock.
Oh wow, we're actually kind of limited here.
Guess we gotta go down.
And you know what?
The next time I find an enemy...
I'm gonna try a sea of lava.
Mr. Rat?
What do you say to this?
Holy shit!
Wow, okay, that's a lot.
Okay!
That was a cool symbol in the center too.
Similar to the one that appeared when you leave.
The mountain or whatever, right?
But I didn't pay attention to what symbol it was.
Well, that's a lot of lava, did not expect that.
Let's blow this up.
Wait, I don't have enough power for that.
Blow it up with that!
Damn, that's a big one.
Fireball is amazing.
Okay.
Hello!
Sir?
Oh my god, I can't hit.
There we go.
I love the way they firecrack when they die or get hit.
Pretty cool effect.
For some reason, this music reminds me of Starcraft music right now.
Like the Terran theme.
A little bit with the guitar riff.
Sir!
He almost hit me with that.
Nice.
Oh no!
I'm okay.
I don't know how I just put fire to this coal.
Don't hit the rat.
I am the one who hits the rats.
I think that rat is about to die.
Oh, don't stand in the lava.
Let's use the good old...
You know what?
Let's try this again here.
How much does it reveal again?
Only my screen, right?
Yeah, close to my screen.
Like that area, sort of.
Oh, that bounced on him!
Not bad!
Wait, is...
Oh no, I was about to say, is everything revealed?
But it's actually not.
I kind of want to use Sea of Lava everywhere.
I was about to say, I want to find a large pool of water and use Sea of Lava.
Let's try this.
But there's...
There's...
Rusted Metal and shit.
Let's try it.
Oh, of course.
It would create a bunch of obsidian.
I mean, rock.
Right there.
Oopsie!
We're fine.
Let's wait for this.
Patient?
Precise?
Come on.
Sirp.
We barely dodged that.
If I had a cap on, that would have penetrated my cap.
Close.
Nice.
Come here.
You want to dance?
Okay, you don't want to.
It's a blah blah.
What the hell is he doing?
109 HP?
Not bad.
Still above 100.
Quick maths.
Why is that rock suspicious looking?
Get out of here.
Don't like...
That thing is buried in there.
Hold on.
It's time for the all-seeing eye.
Ah.
Ah!
Oh, wait.
What's happening up here?
There's some kind of enemy with an aura.
Aura enemy.
Can I get up there some other way?
Maybe via this path?
Go like this.
Uh-oh.
He killed himself.
He loved to see it.
That was pro.
Watch this.
God, that's so cool.
And now everything is going to be free for me to grab that wand.
Look at the lava burning through.
The gray rock and the coal being, actually.
Up.
Can I get in here?
Ah!
The one place I shouldn't go...
Pssst.
Oh, shit.
Okay, what do we have?
A rock?
A digging bolt?
A summoned rock spirit?
And a plasma beam?
An instantaneous dangerous beam of light?
I'm liking the sound of that.
Not gonna lie.
Let's try it.
Ah, but wait.
It has a bunch of shit on it, right?
So...
And it's shuffle.
Don't know about that one, bro.
Ah, man.
Should I replace this one?
Maybe not, right?
Uh... shit, I don't know.
Maybe this one.
Fuck this.
I mean, I used all of the Sea of Lava anyway and the dropper bolt.
Eh.
Whatever.
I can live without the dropper bolt for now.
I'll have another opportunity later on, I'm sure.
But you know what?
Let's just try this.
Yo!
That must have been the digging bolt.
That's one of those things?
Rock spirit.
Autonomous rock ally.
Oh!
Right.
It explodes.
I think I knew of that, actually.
Just kind of forgot.
Water?
Uh...
hello.
Shit, shit, shit.
I forgot my once.
What do I have?
Uh, three.
Yo!
Bro!
Wait, is this shuffle?
Oh, you're dead.
You're not dead!
Incredible.
Ah!
Shit.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Ah, that hurt.
This is actually bad.
You gotta be dead.
Finally.
And now we shoot a small one.
I'm burning.
Psst!
Ah!
This is not easy.
It's not easy.
Blah blah!
Okay.
It's going pretty well so far, I'd say.
I kind of want to experiment with the plasma beam soon.
Whoopsie daisy.
Would you like some?
Oi!
You have gold, right?
Hand it over.
What the hell is this?
Oh wait, is that where I started?
Let's see.
It's gotta be.
Blow this up.
You know what?
Let's blow this up.
Use... my number three.
Hup!
And then we go through here.
Ah, let's wait a bit.
For the fireworks.
Oh, but wait.
I can't get...
Uh, this does not make a hole, right?
Sort of.
Ah, no, it doesn't.
Crap!
It's okay.
200 gold, I would like more.
Shh!
Shit, that was a nice shot there.
I can't hit anything.
There we go.
Where the hell did I come from?
Oh, I came from here.
That is correct.
Can I kick this again?
Boom!
Ha ha!
So badass.
You can do some really badass stuff in this game.
Ah, this is all dissolved.
Don't really like that.
Let's go this way.
Ho ho!
Hello!
Bye bye!
Whoa!
Nice shot!
Ah, but wait, my gold is ripped.
Oh, wait, we've got...
Ho!
Shit!
What just exploded?
Oh!
That was sick.
Like, the pickup radius is a little larger than the radius for getting...
I want.
Burn it!
Oh, I can't.
Shit.
Uh, we do have a digging bolt on this, but there's a bit of a chance that it's not going to come out.
I'm going to try.
Blap!
Yeah.
This thing's going to blow up in my face.
Don't do it.
Hey!
A mysterious darkness lingers in this place.
Hold on.
Do something.
What if I shoot it?
What if I put water on it?
Okay.
What if I worm-firm on it?
Wait, is it still there?
It is.
Weird.
Uh, how am I going to get in there?
I probably just go around.
How about that?
I'm an idiot.
Shit.
It's as easy as that.
Whoa!
Hot damn, he's throwing lava.
Oh, he killed himself.
That's what happens when you throw lava.
Don't throw lava.
Levitation potion.
Not bad.
I like that.
Uh, what is happening down there?
Something crazy is go- It's a ghost buzzer.
Hello.
See ya.
Bye-bye.
I should be careful.
Oh shit, what the fuck?
Ah!
We got hit by the teleportation.
We're burning!
We're not burning.
This is getting dangerous.
It's- It's ogre.
There's no way we're going to survive this.
I don't know what this is!
Oh my lord!
Roboticute projectile.
Ah shit.
Bro, this place is nuts!
Last time I was in here, it was a clusterfuck too.
I remember being hit with the teleportation potion in here too last time.
And it fucked me up completely.
Ah, damn.
Okay, okay.
First death doesn't count, remember?
Alright.
This time, we have a firebolt, and that means...
Blop!
Yeah, that works.
Yeah.
Something just blew up in the distance.
I don't know what that was.
Also, what do I have here?
Water.
Okay, so I can't make a mud mountain.
I don't need to, actually.
Oh shit!
Oh wait a minute, this doesn't explode on impact?
Oh it does.
Man, this wand sucks.
It's not that good.
It's a shit wand.
But it's possible to do.
Just takes a bit of patience.
Nice.
I can probably shoot two of them.
Shit.
One is enough.
Okay, we gotta clear some more.
Actually, a significant upgrade you get up here.
That HP is just...
A little
higher.
Come on, almost there.
Yeah!
Blop!
I'll even take this with me.
125, baby.
And then we have... Bouncing Burst.
Ah man, where's that one...
uh, spell that I had in the very first time I played this game?
Like a bouncing ball that didn't disappear after a while.
I forgot what it was called.
But my god, that's a good spell.
It one shots most enemies in here.
But that's not bad either, it's okay, you know?
It's what it is.
The hell is this now?
Okay, hold on.
Let's blow it.
Oh, that's... Flammoxium.
Right.
Let me try...
Oh, never mind, I don't want to try anything.
Flammoxium sucks.
Uh oh, it's coming down.
Ah, that's some bullshit, I don't like Flammoxium.
Blow it up!
But there's gotta be another gameplay reason for it to be here, right?
Maybe you can combine it.
And there's all these powders... Oh, chest, nice.
Nice!
Fucking HP out the wazoo here!
We've got a hammers.
Does life get any better right now?
I don't think so.
And look at this!
We can sort of just go to the surface almost.
Let's just clear it.
There, axis acquired.
And we're up.
That's pretty cool.
I like it.
Let's see what's over here.
I think I know what's over here.
Uh, never mind.
I do not know what's over there.
Let's go down.
Okay.
Where's the lava?
Hey, hortas!
Ah, shit!
Dammit, that was bad.
Oh, that is toxic sludge potion.
Whoa!
Awesome!
That was great.
Yeah, you don't want to get close quarter with these guys.
That's just bad for your health.
That's another lesson.
Never go close with the horta.
Oh, there's one more.
They were stacked.
They were hugging.
Hugging him is...
That guy is mega confused.
He's so flummoxed right now.
Imagine just going around in real life saying that word instead of strange.
Or weird, you say, man, that was really flummoxed what just happened, you know?
You look very flummoxed today.
Sounds so hilarious.
There's a dude trapped in there, so I'm just going to leave him.
You're going to be trapped there.
I don't care.
Ah, horta.
Two wants.
Wow.
Yeah, that's fine.
Easy.
Love it.
Got another potion.
Flummoxium.
What's this?
Levitation.
Yo, I want that.
In fact, let me try something.
Flummoxium goes in here.
Just sits at the bottom.
What if I add water?
Does anything happen?
I want to grab that tele...
Oh, dude.
I have an idea.
Watch this.
Let me get rid of the flummoxium.
Somewhere.
Where's a good place to dispose of it?
Over here.
Dispose of the flummoxium?
Actually, I can just...
No, I was about to throw the bottle, but that's not what I want.
I want to empty it.
Just relieving myself here a little bit.
There we go.
I'm going to use this.
Grab all of it.
Oh, I'm so flummoxed.
That's fine.
Oh, it's so weird.
Wait.
Oh, you levitate 75% faster.
Okay.
I didn't realize there was an actual number I could read there.
Oh, my God.
This flummoxium is messing with me.
Give me all of this.
Now, watch.
I'm going to go outside.
And I'm going to go up to the worm.
But I'm going to go higher.
As high as it gets.
If I can even make it.
Actually, hold on.
I do have bombs on me, so I can actually just make holes.
Never mind.
But I'm going to do it anyway.
How much do I have?
47% levitation.
That's fine.
Hey!
Okay, watch this.
Cheers, everybody.
The Friday of all Fridays is today.
Look at how they bounce in a parabola.
This is a parabola, it looks like.
So it's funny how they, you know.
Those who know, they know.
Don't want to elaborate on that.
Oh, it hit him!
Why is that a hurta here?
The hell?
What are you doing, sir?
He's going to go here?
In fact, I'm going to grab this egg anyway.
Right.
Let me just take another peek in here.
You know what?
I don't remember if I tried this.
I think I tried this last time, but I'm not sure.
Let's leave it there.
Hold on.
Wait, you can't make a hole, so I have to try this.
Okay, okay, okay, cool.
There is something up there.
Fuck yeah.
Let's see.
So many wiggling eggs?
I don't want that.
Gimme eggs!
Oh, it's the top.
Hello!
Ooh!
Oh, I thought I could stand on that.
That is a flaming ball.
Is that a bomb?
Huh.
Fungus.
And this bleeds.
What exactly?
What is this?
This is slime, right?
Right.
They explode.
Man, another one of these fucking things.
The hell?
Sir?
Fuck out of here.
Oh.
Reviving now, boys.
It was a fucking musical instrument.
Hey, that's fucking awesome.
Whoops.
Alright, well, that was weird.
What do we have over here, though?
Excuse me?
The hell is this?
These look like...
Oh, what?
Man, hold on.
What does this say?
Four?
Let me squint my eyes.
Four...
Y...
S...
X...
No, wait, these are not...
These are some kind of runes.
WO?
Are these small faces?
The hell am I looking at?
Let's try this.
He is not my friend.
He is just off somewhere now.
In fact...
Off you go.
A whole family of worms.
Oh, that's a biggie!
Kind of want to kill him.
Is that crazy?
Alright, I have released some bullshit.
Let me see what's down here.
Oh, that's deep.
You know what?
Drink this and go...
Shh...
Maximum speed.
Snowy wasteland.
The air feels freezing.
Yo!
The hell is that?
Tell me I can get in there.
Oh, this is going to take a while.
Oh, wait, they have bombs.
They have bombs.
I mean, from up here?
Will they roll a bit?
Look how pro I am.
Okay.
Fuck yeah!
The hell is this?
Pah-ha-sil-me.
It's an eye.
This eye-shaped artifact projects a malevolent glare.
What the f...
What?
Oh!
Okay!
A very deathly stare.
Wow!
Hold on a second.
Interesting.
Let me, uh...
Get up here again.
Is this gonna do anything here?
Oh!
Hello!
What the fuck is this?
It's a wand.
Can't tell.
Uh, wait, it...
How many...
Wait, there's no slots on?
Wait, what's happening?
Oh!
Whoa!
Twenty!
Can't...
Node A?
Node D?
D sharp, I think that means?
I don't know what any of this means.
Music for your ears.
Okay.
Wait, is this like a musical instrument?
Where I can technically make any music I want if I just play this in the right order?
Like, let's say I put this in the right order and I just hold it down, maybe I can make some music with that.
That's probably what happens, but I can't edit this in now, unfortunately.
Okay, that's super weird.
Let's see what's over here.
Yo, it made a hole right through the damn tree!
Pretty cool!
What the hell am I finding, dude?
Look at this!
Why is there an eye, Para Silume?
Projects a malevolent glare.
What if I...
Okay.
I'm just gonna sit there and burn?
You know what?
I have a feeling, if I play a certain music combination here, something will happen.
Right?
There's gotta be a secret with that.
If you play a certain combination of musical notes, maybe that thing will do something.
Well, I can use this to dig through snow, I guess.
Pretty neat.
I'm stuck.
Shit!
Okay, I'm fine, I'm fine.
Never mind.
Everything's fine.
So, why was this unlike a weird-ass brickwork here in the middle of the snowy place?
Damn.
Why is everything shaking?
I'm intrigued.
Oh...
Hell no.
I don't think I can do this.
This is way too advanced for me.
I could get through that with my eye.
What the hell is this?
Yo, wait, is that a statue of me?
Look!
Doesn't it kinda look like me?
What do we have up here?
Something.
Just a giant...
Hold on.
Oh!
Is there anything up there?
Six percent.
I have no more.
This is the last.
Okay.
Okay?
Weird.
Let me try and get rid of this.
I mean, alright.
You know what?
Let me try and cut this off.
See what happens.
I'm a little stuck here again.
Shit.
Wait, what's happening?
Did you hear the sound?
There was a sound just now.
Oh, it's the O2!
I see, I see, I see, I understand.
I understand.
Fuck, I lost a bunch of HP.
Oh, god damn it.
Oh, no.
I'm an idiot.
All the steam.
Okay.
Cool.
The he- Oh, no.
I mean, we're here to explore.
This is all fine.
Oh.
Got a little flag here.
Damn!
Taken care of by the eye.
Okay.
I am just out here exploring.
I have no ambitions of getting anywhere in this run.
This is simply curiosity right now.
Oh, another one.
The hell?
Let's leave it.
Oh, here we go, here we go.
The hell is that?
Let me in.
Actually super useful.
Wait, I'm about to- O2!
Hold on, I need to wait.
Shit.
Come here.
I gotta be careful here.
I can suffocate easily.
Essence- Oh, wait.
Essence eater?
The hell is this?
Essence eater.
Oh, wait a minute.
I think I saw one of these before, didn't I?
And when I shot it, it exploded.
Essence eater.
Maybe it absorbs some kind of essence.
Maybe like water or something?
If I can fill my bottle?
Hmm, I'm going to leave that there for now.
Don't want to blow it up again.
So quiet here too.
Dude, I'm just so excited to see what I'm going to find over here.
This whole area feels like a massive secret, you know?
I could have gone through the snow a little while back and actually into the- Was that one of my projectiles being reflected?
And into the area with the enemies, but I didn't do it because they looked scary.
Uh, what the hell is that green thing?
What?
I burned it.
I don't know what that was.
Ooh.
Wait, is this- Is this a- This is a collapsed bridge!
Holy shit!
There's enemies.
Uh-oh.
Oh, this is- This is- This is- This is bad!
Ah, it's ripped.
It's ripped.
There's no way.
There is no way, Jose.
So, I guess the plan is to come back here after being in the snowy level.
Because we can actually come back here.
Frozen vault!
Ah, fuck!
Nah, I'm stuck.
Oh, yeah, man, that's ripped.
I expected that.
Shit, I should have tried my eye on them.
Why didn't I do that?
Shit!
Material acid.
Okay.
Crap.
Alright, well...
That was fun!
Now I know that there's some stuff over there.
Very important.
Snow potion!
Cool.
And I have bombs, so I can't get up there, unfortunately.
So we just keep moving.
Just keep going.
Ah, spark bolt again.
Actually, spark bolt is fine.
I don't mind spark bolt.
Spark bolt is like my second favorite.
Of the starting things you can get.
Ah, not getting that.
Definitely.
Sir, this is for you.
How did that not explode?
Oh.
Nice.
Now we take it slow, and explore, and get money, and move on.
Find some wands.
Find some gold.
The standard stuff.
Kiva skeevy.
Is that the same thing?
This tiny...
Yeah, this is...
It's so weird.
Let me try and put it in here.
Just removes the water.
Actually kind of useful, I guess.
If you were into that sort of thing.
What happens if I just spray snow somewhere?
The snow gets there where you spray it.
Makes sense.
Hey, snow.
You like snow?
He probably hates snow.
Watch.
Shit!
Snow me up.
Snow me.
Okay.
Yeah, okay.
He...
He likes the snow.
Unfortunately.
So that's not good.
At least now I know that.
Where is he?
Oh my god!
I'm dying.
This is over.
Holy crap.
Let's just not tangle with him right now.
If I can choose to avoid it, I will.
Wait, where'd he go?
He died!
No, the money!
I think he blew himself up somehow.
Maybe he was too close when he threw one of his dastardly bolts.
There's a wand up there on the left.
I see it.
Oh my god.
Didn't mean to set that on fire.
It is what it is.
How do I get there?
Probably with a bomb.
Oh no, I can go below.
Good.
Thank you.
Ah, close...
Oh, there's a heart!
Ah shit, I can't...
I'm sorry!
Oh my god, you can totally kill enemies!
By throwing things on them!
That's so good!
I kind of want to pick them up and just throw them around.
It seemed like it was one-shotting.
Uh, look at this.
Okay, maybe they need some momentum.
He doesn't get hit just by touching it.
Ah!
Yeah, just be careful here.
There we go.
Hey, miss!
Where'd you come from?
Thank you.
Okay, so I'm going to use a bomb to get in there.
Let's see if I can put this in a nice spot.
Maybe we can wedge it in here somehow.
If I stand here and go plop.
Wait, what happened?
Oh, what the hell?
Where did that bomb go?
That was so confusing!
It must have clipped into the wall or something.
Uh...
Sir?
What the hell?
Someone has a wand.
It's you!
Shit.
Oh, you're easy.
Give me that.
Disc projectile.
Very nice.
I think that's a good wand.
Well, that's an excellent wand!
Ho-ho!
Ah, let's not grab that.
Shit.
Bro, this thing is nuts.
Oh, it's so good!
Fuck!
That's excellent!
I'm on fire!
Snow me, snow me, snow me, snow me!
Okay.
25 HP, though.
Ooh, that's a bad start.
This is my primary wand now.
I think these can hit me, so I gotta be extra careful here.
Uh, wait, did I just take damage from walking over...
my projectiles?
No, that was some poison, okay.
I thought it was sharp, so I took damage.
They one-shot these guys.
Not bad at all!
Oh, this is gonna be a slaughter.
I'm so sorry, Hamises.
Ho, be careful.
There we go.
Money.
Hamises, I'm sorry.
Gotcha.
It's for your own good.
Actually, it's for my own good, but, you know.
It is what it is!
Wand for me!
I need a bomb?
But how the hell can I even do this?
If I go up along here and to the left, that's probably how I'm gonna do this.
Unless, hold on, I didn't see this little area.
Ooh!
Oh, okay!
So we definitely gotta throw this in here.
Have fun!
Nice!
The little fire thingy comes in handy.
I keep expecting something to explode here.
Doesn't that wand kinda look like a crossbow?
Fucking hell, it's one of these again.
I'll take it though.
Don't mind.
Ooh, that's electricity, look!
Oh, you can actually see it on the symbol, I guess.
There's a little lightning symbol.
Uh, I can also go to the left here.
Should I be doing that?
Hold on, can I?
Be careful with that torch.
Let's go in here.
God, it's so good!
Lovely wand I found there.
Doesn't get much better than this, for the beginning.
Okay.
Oh, it's the enemy.
Have fun.
Did he die?
Oh, he fell all the way down.
Go here.
Chest!
Oh, it's sick!
Let's get it.
There's a wand inside.
The hell is that?
Mist of spirits, a cloud of potent alcohol.
The hell?
Oh, shit!
Wait, what?
Oh, I'm alcoholic now.
Oh, acid trail.
Wait a minute.
Is this always going to catch fire then?
Hold on.
No, it's just alcohol.
I mean, if I want to get drunk...
that's how to do it, I guess.
Just inhale the vapes.
What's that?
Rusted metal?
Okay, we've been there.
Oops!
What did you come from?
Sir?
I'm dying.
I'm almost dead.
I'm actually going to die.
I couldn't get past here.
Look at the bullshit.
Oh, my God.
No!
What a death.
Goddamn.
But you know what?
I'm happy with it, because that means I get to start like this now.
Yo!
That's a sick one.
Right, the magic missile, I haven't had that in a while.
That's actually a sick spell.
In fact, I would like that to be unlimited.
Magic missile all the way, baby.
That's what I say.
Is me or is this mountain especially high today?
You know what I mean?
I can probably hit it from here, too.
It's like straight up.
Yay!
Look at that.
Nice.
Man, this thing just rolled downhill, huh?
Oh, you know what?
Oops.
Oh, never mind.
Keep moving.
Spark bolts and magic missile.
That will do.
And there's a one right below me.
So now let's fucking play this carefully now.
Let's follow the tenets of the Masters of old.
We have been playing loose and fast with the rules lately here.
And it's unacceptable.
It's time to get back on track, damn it.
Which means no more excessive risk-taking.
Even though it's fun.
There we go.
See, that was a bit of a risk-taking then.
That was fun.
But I shall not do that again.
Look at this.
Another magic missile.
Hey, nice.
Not bad at all.
What a start.
Let's go all the way to the left first.
See what we have.
Just a mine cart.
There's something satisfying about kicking metal objects.
So this one is actually decent because it shoots fast.
I'm liking the wand.
The hell is this place?
We gotta blow it up.
Gain access to what's below.
You know what, I'm gonna let this cook for a while and then I'm gonna go the other way.
Nah.
I'm not.
I changed my mind.
Because this wood is almost done.
Fire's gonna go out.
There we go.
Okay.
Taking care of.
Enemies.
There's one below me.
I'm gonna blow up.
Oh my god.
There, you like that?
See, I'm not sure if I should be blowing these things up just like I'm doing here.
Oh, almost caught fire.
Because one, yeah, they will be destroyed and they won't explode on me by chance later on.
But it also provides a lot of chance to catch fire, right?
So it's a bit of a double-edged sword.
That gold is too risky to get.
I'm not getting it.
These are the tenets that we follow.
Put it into the oil.
Haha!
I don't know why that was so entertaining.
I like having minecarts in oil.
In fact, name one thing that doesn't get improved by being inside of oil.
I challenge you.
Oh, we've got a dude.
But I have things here.
Oh, one shot, baby!
That was risky.
Wait, what?
This is not water.
This ain't water.
Ah, shit!
Oh, too late, I found blood.
Ah, that's unfortunate.
See, I shouldn't have taken that gold.
It was too enticing.
I saw all the gold.
I was like, oh, oh, oh, gotta have it, gotta have it.
I need to stop that train of thought immediately.
Invisibilium potion.
Not bad.
Why am I carrying around this thing?
Sir, you know what?
Hey!
Where are you?
I'm going to try and throw it on him.
Sir?
Here, you like that?
He actually fucking died.
It rolled.
I'm sorry, Hamis.
I'm just finding all kinds of inventive ways to murder Hamis today.
It's crazy.
Hamis, come here.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Hamis.
Let me take you out of your misery.
Okay.
Ah, pheromone potion?
Hmm, I'll take it.
Sure.
Give me all the pheromone.
My gut...
Get away from me.
Oh, he died.
Nice.
Hand it over.
I'm going to go up here now.
Look at all these Hamises.
They're drunk on oil.
So that means fire is especially harmful.
See, I see the gold and I ignore it.
At least that one.
This one up here I can take.
Nice.
A big vat of oil.
Uh...
That's a massive suspicious looking boulder, isn't it?
Is that just me?
Hold on.
Boulder's gone.
These things scared the crap out of me when I'm in melee range.
They jumped so quick.
Oh, Hamis.
You also scared the crap out of me again.
The second time today.
I guess I deserve it after I've murdered all your family.
Another horta?
No, horta.
Hold on.
I need to remind myself.
HORTA!
Steel trap memory, folks.
That's me.
I never forget a thing.
And that's facts.
Hey.
Hand it over.
Hand over that lunch money.
I'm such a bully.
I could get in here.
Ah!
I can get in over here.
Look at that little bush acting like it's closing it off, but it's not.
It's like a little secret area here.
Filled with nothing.
I mean ten gold.
Nothing to scoff at.
I do appreciate ten gold.
It's better than nine.
And that's facts.
You heard it right here.
Okay.
You know what?
I'm lazy.
Man, am I that lazy?
Yeah, I am.
I'm committed.
That was very lazy of me.
So hold on.
Why is there this big...
I need to blow it up.
I just need to.
It's too entertaining to look at.
I'm gonna take a sip while I watch this chaos unfold.
Look how fucking good this fire looks.
In a game that's only made of these little pixels here.
If you know what I mean, right?
It's incredible.
What they've achieved.
I can't get over the different shit that happens here and how it's happening.
Here's this fire.
If you squint your eyes, this fire looks extremely realistic.
In fact, if you close your eyes and imagine realistic fire, this is really realistic.
Okay, I think it's safe now.
Go!
Polymorphine, why am I going out of my way to grab that?
I'm getting it.
Someone's behind me.
It's Barney.
Come on!
Ah, I've got that.
Okay, fine.
I'll come out and get you.
Alright, we move on.
Nah, it's a dead end.
Shit.
It's fine.
It's going pretty well so far, I think.
Hold on, I have a bunch of liquids.
Excuse me.
Wait a minute, what does it say?
Oh, chaotic?
Polymorphine.
I read it as just polymorphine.
The hell?
So I actually like that.
I like the chaotic version, because it can come in quite handy.
If I need to blow up walls and stuff, there's a good chance I'll be turned into something that can do that.
Barney?
You've had enough?
Time to go home.
You're not driving, are you?
So that's the end of the line?
Where is the lava area?
Oh, is it right here?
Ha!
When you speak of the sun.
No, wait, when you speak of the devil is the expression in English.
Another one.
Is this the same?
It's always the same.
Okay, it's Mardina.
I have acceleration potion.
Watch.
Ha ha ha!
Oh, this got a little bit scary there.
I was a little bit too eager.
Oh, but wait.
We're going to spawn something.
But that's fine, because I have... it's fine.
I have acceleration, I can quickly back, right?
Yo!
Invisibilium.
That's what I'm doing.
I'm going to grab the thing invisibilium out of here.
In fact, acceleration invisibilium, and then we go... easy mode, easy clap.
Yeah, I'll take it.
Extra HP.
Why is it called familiar orb of true knowledge?
That's what I wonder.
Oh, you know what, actually?
See, this is an altar, right?
Of sorts.
Or like a stage.
Wait, was this always here?
Yeah, it was.
Oh.
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
Okay, it's time.
Let's do this.
Two, two, two, two.
Oh!
Oh, I can't mix... I mixed these in my stomach, and I became sick.
Interesting.
I'm greased lightning now.
I don't know what's better, invisibilium or...
Maybe the boss will see through my invisibility, you know?
That's what I'm afraid of.
But I'm gonna do it anyway.
Let's try the invisibilium.
Nothing to it, then try it, right?
Oh, wait, I'm...
Oh, wait, I have to...
Wait, what?
Oh!
I can't ingest it.
I see.
I need to pour it on myself.
Okay.
I understand.
Shit, okay, fine.
There we go.
Let's go!
Is he not coming?
Wait, what?
Why is he not here?
Alright!
Easy clap!
I don't know why that just worked like that, but I don't complain.
This is fine.
I shall not look a gift horse in the mouth.
Alright, dude.
My theory there is that I was invisible, so the monster didn't see me, so he never spawned.
That's what I think.
I mean, it makes sense, if you think about it.
Are you thinking about it?
Okay, good.
Polymor... Oh, that... Oh, this is the one I saw.
So I saw that and I picked up chaotic somewhere else.
I must have really gaslighted myself there.
That was more often than you'd think.
I can get in here.
I'm not done with this place, man.
I need more money.
Ah, wait, this is... Ah, I don't want to destroy that.
Ah, okay, fine.
It is what it is.
Let's go somewhere else.
And that money's gone, unfortunately.
I have 300 gold.
It's a good start.
I think when I reach 20 HP is the point where I'm like, okay, it's time to go back, you know?
Or through the portal.
Crit!
Hold on, that did 15 damage.
How much does this do?
So, X5?
I have to pay attention if that's always the case or if it's like a randomized damage number that is higher.
But times five is kind of insane.
Usually crits in games is like times two, right?
Wait, what is this?
Oh, wait, I... It's mine.
I left it here.
Right.
I thought it was a new one.
Health!
Oh, this is great.
I'm gonna get in there.
Wait, I can't get... Oh, the damp rock.
I guess I entered from up here.
Oh, but there's lava up there.
Shit!
Man, this whole place is bulletproof.
Let me go from below.
Maybe that's gonna work.
Let me stain myself a bit here.
Oh, yeah, this is gonna work for sure.
Hamish somehow survived that.
Sir?
Come on!
Oh, wow!
Okay, it didn't hit me.
Felt like it did.
Got a want.
It's a good run so far!
Slimeball.
That's actually a decent spell.
I like it.
You can use it to dig.
And you use it to kill.
In fact, it does a lot of damage.
I'm not gonna use it.
I need speed.
Dammit, that's not what I meant to do.
Shit!
How did I miss that?
Wait, there's a drop off on this projectile.
I thought it was flying a straight line.
Rocket propelled.
This?
Flammoxium.
So many potions!
You know what?
I'm gonna try and do some mixing here.
Let's put acceleration.
In here.
Let's put some... What do we have?
Invicellium plus vomit potion?
That's nasty, bro!
Let's do it.
Okay.
What's this?
Pheromone?
It's just a layered mass now.
You can actually tell which ones are more dense than the others.
It's kind of cool how they line up in layers like that, right?
Pretty neat.
And it won't surprise me if that is all simulated correct.
Like, it's just all live, you know?
Holy crap, there's a conundrum going on up there.
Or a congregation I'm in.
But I guess it's also a conundrum.
Why they're all there.
Hold on, what is my... Oh, it's that one.
Maybe I do want to use this.
Oh, you like slime?
Me too.
My slime is deadlier than yours.
My mucus is superior.
I can blow my way through that wall up there, I think.
That's wood?
Perfect.
Yeah!
And then... Oh, they're all going to come out, huh?
That's actually kind of unfortunate.
Guys?
What the hell are you doing?
Let's kill him.
Oh, shotgun dudes!
You did.
Nice.
He's going to die from fire.
Come on.
There we go.
Very cool.
Blah blah.
15 crit again.
So I think it's always times five.
At least with this wand.
Dude, that means crits are actually insane.
That means I need to cover myself in blood more.
Blood blood blood.
Another magic missile?
Are you kidding?
I'll take it.
Let me see here.
I need to be careful.
This is a shuffle.
But I guess they all are shuffles, so it doesn't really matter too much.
Hmm.
I like the stats on this, but it only has one slot, right?
So it's not that great.
So maybe I'll just replace this one.
Since it's empty anyway, right?
Seems like a good choice.
We have a horta.
Excuse me, horta.
Little secret area, it seems.
There's some gold.
The hell is happening there?
Burn it up!
Give me the gold.
Shit, I can't reach it.
I like that I keep finding these magic missiles when I run out of the...
previous ones, you know?
They gave it like, here, have some more.
Thanks, I will.
That's gonna blow up majorly now.
Or not.
It is, it's burning.
Watch.
I'm gonna sip while I watch this unfold.
Ah, beautiful.
Just beautiful.
Ah!
Why did I do that?
I'm an idiot.
Wait, the...
Not in the work!
Aw, man.
Fuck.
That was so dumb of me.
Okay, it's time to head down.
We're leaving.
We are leaving this place.
Also, I need to see here.
I have chaotic...
Chaotic polymorphine is the one to get...
is the one to use.
If I am on fire again, that's the one.
What's up, hammers?
So many hammers!
Oh, that, you know what?
No, I'm not taking that.
It's too risky.
There's acid down there.
Don't like it.
Alright, let's go down.
Find a portal.
Down, down, down, down, down.
Uh, give me blood.
Shit!
Oh, man, he jumped fast!
That was scary.
That almost went real bad.
Uh, there's the portal.
I could just jump in, I guess.
Kinda wanna kill him, though.
Fuck you.
Got him.
There it is.
Let's go.
Not bad.
We found a bunch of HP.
185.
Yo.
That's great.
Not bad at all.
Okay, let's see what we got here.
What's this?
Black hole!
I tried that one once, remember?
We found a wand with that.
Oh, but only three of them.
Okay.
Hold on, let me see the perks.
It's perk time, baby.
What do we got?
More hatred?
No.
Dissolve powders.
Sand and other soft powdery materials dissolve quickly in your...
See, why is that...
Why is that a perk?
Like, why is that good?
I don't understand.
Iron stomach.
You no longer suffer from negative effects of eating.
I don't like any of these.
We're gonna...
Hold on before I do that.
I have 400 monies.
Let's see if there's any essentials that I want here.
Dynamite is cool.
Honestly, disc projectiles...
I think I want those.
We can do one re-roll.
Yeah.
Let's see.
Loki mutation.
You grow curious additional limbs that fight for you.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
Fungal disease.
When near danger, you sprout fungal growths.
And low recoil.
Recoil caused by your spells is greatly reduced.
But your spells fly slightly slower.
I don't like any of these.
Uh...
I just heard something nasty.
Maybe I'll do the Loki mutation.
Let's try that.
Uh...
What the fuck?
Holy shit, that's nasty looking!
Hello?
I thought it was floating for a second.
No, no, no, it's actually connecting to the...
Look at that!
Yikes!
Okay, that's gonna change a lot.
I don't have muscle memory to play like this, man.
I can still float, it seems.
Haha, okay.
What's this?
Long distance cast?
The hell is that?
Cast the spells some distance away from the caster.
Uh...
Okay.
It's a utility.
Is it like...
Wait.
I understand.
I get it.
That's cool!
I like it.
Uh...
I don't know what I want, though.
I think I'm just gonna...
So let's see here, .17.
.05.
That's a fast one.
Let me do that.
Okay.
Not bad, but...
Long delay in between shots, though.
That's better.
Yeah, I'm doing that.
This is my primary damage dealer now.
Definitely want this.
Wait, nothing I have can do it!
No!
I don't have enough mana on my ones.
It takes 180.
That's crazy.
Aw, man.
170.
160.
Aw, crap.
That's fine.
Uh...
Man, my ones suck.
How about I rock some...
God, I don't even know.
Dynamite.
God, this is so weird with these limbs.
Let me have that as well.
Have a good old rock.
And...
Let me try this one again.
What the hell is this even?
An empty...
See, okay.
So is it...
Can I specify the spell?
Is that how that works?
God, this is so...
I hate looking at my character.
I'm sorry, but...
I hate spiders.
And this just reminds me so much of the spiders...
that walk around like this.
This is...
This is not making me happy.
I feel like almost restarting, because I don't like how this...
I can't stand looking at it.
It's just...
It...
God, it's disturbing.
I'm gonna try, though.
Put this here.
Uh...
I don't even know.
That one there, sure.
What is the deal with this?
Wait.
Wait, 60...
What do you mean, 65?
What?
60...
Wait, why is it doing so much damage?
In fact, why can I see the damage?
I don't see damage when I do this.
What the fuck?
Hold on.
Some is an otherwise empty egg that casts a spell.
So it's like a random spell that comes out?
So it's predetermined what spell this one casts every...
It's...
It does some kind of spell that does a lot of damage, it seems.
Uh...
Okay, let's just move.
I'm gonna get used to this.
Holy shit.
Crap, this looks so nasty.
Really well done, though.
This is so well designed, I gotta say.
Nah, this is...
This is not working out for me, man.
I mean...
It's actually really useful.
I'm not gonna lie, it looks fucked up when you move around.
Alright, I can get used to this.
It's fine, it's fine.
I just crit that guy for a bunch.
The good part is, it's so easy to avoid all kinds of things.
Shit.
I mean, there's the portal.
Don't go in, don't go in, don't go in.
Fuck.
Wait, I have very limited...
Wait, how does that work?
Oh, fuck.
In the water.
Chest!
Yeah!
I found a wand.
Energy orb.
Fuck yeah.
That's a good one.
I like it.
I'm gonna keep it.
Bro, this...
Like, my levitation energy is...
Whoa!
Fuck, that scared me.
Why did that just explode?
Maybe it was a mine, I didn't pay attention.
Holy shit.
Okay.
Get in there.
There we go.
Wait, I didn't recharge?
I forgot to recharge...
Oh, I forgot to recharge my spells.
Shit.
Oh, that's bad.
What am I doing, man?
God damn.
I was completely flummoxed...
by these spider legs that I have acquired.
I couldn't think straight.
You know how it is.
When you grow spider legs like that, you tend to forget other things that matter.
All you can think about are these spider legs.
Well, I can just walk along the roof.
What's up, man?
That's fine, I don't care.
I'm sort of speedrunning through this right now, because I wouldn't mind dying, honestly.
I don't like these legs.
And lots of digging bolts, holy crap.
Replace it with...
That one.
Let's see how that works.
Ho!
Wait, why is this so effective?
Wasn't it digging glass that did this last time?
Somehow this is...
really good still.
Awesome!
I like it.
This looks so messed up.
Wait, why can't I get up there?
Wait.
Oh, this is so awkward.
I can't levitate the way you usually think you would be able to.
It doesn't work like that.
You have to walk along the edges, you can't really levitate anymore.
Oh, wait a minute, did it say...
that fight for me?
Does that mean...
this is destroying that thing below me?
Is that what happened before when something exploded?
Did I walk on it?
Oh, shit.
This is so messed up.
Part of me just wants to go through the portal, but I kinda want a little more money.
Otherwise, what is the use, right?
Fight for me!
Come on!
Come on, legs!
Kill him!
Oh my god, you're useless.
What is up here?
That looked nice.
There's nothing there.
Let's keep moving this way.
It's gonna be so hard to dodge projectiles like this.
I can already tell.
Do we
have a spawner?
Money!
Where are you?
This is some cursed shit.
That's the proper word for this situation.
Wait, did it say Peter?
What is his name, Peter?
What just happened there?
I moused over him and it said Peter, I think.
Unless I probably misread that.
You know what?
Let's use this opportunity to go nuts in the fungal caverns.
If we die, we die.
It is what it is.
I don't care.
I want to see what the hell is going on in here.
We gotta blow that up to get in.
That's beautiful.
We've got a ghost buster!
What is this?
Acceleration.
I need you to be careful that it's not teleportation.
Dude, I'm moving so quick.
Look at this cursed shit.
The hell is that?
Yo, what the hell is this?
I'm kinda stuck here.
I'm stuck.
Come on, Lex!
Fight for me!
I really should use a different weapon for this.
But I don't know what I have right now.
What do I have?
Honestly, maybe this?
Does it do damage?
It does.
Oh, I can...
I keep forgetting I have this!
I can just do that!
Oh my god!
Yeah!
This is so messed up!
This is a terrible fate.
To be a spider.
That is the flaming egg thingy.
Got a mage.
Uh oh, uh oh!
Hopefully I hit him.
Hopefully he died.
He affects me with this bullshit.
It lasts so long!
Can I cleanse that?
Hold on.
Okay.
Didn't do anything.
Man, that enemy is something else, isn't it?
Bunch of gold, though.
This is actually a great source of gold if you want to...
have a lot of gold for the next area, right?
Ah shit!
Not these things.
Wait, am I flummoxed?
No.
God, I hate those little creatures.
Already.
One of the worst.
Shit!
Bro, you've got some HP.
Why does it take so little damage?
Oh, wow.
Uh, you know what?
Let me use this.
Yo, that thing blows up walls and stuff.
The hell?
Oh, I thought it was blowing up my projectiles.
But it's actually, they run out after a while.
What is this?
A double spell with slime ball.
Hmm.
I'm not sure I like this very much.
This wand right here.
Also, it's shuffle, right?
Yeah, let's take it.
Don't like shuffle.
Shuffle bad.
I just blew up pheromone plus toxic sludge.
Do it again.
They're my friends now, right?
Sup, friends?
I'm going to kill them still because they have money.
Yo, that's very effective.
Oh, never mind.
They are back.
Oh, shit!
Holy shit, the HP on these guys!
Yeah, I'm almost dead.
What's this?
Fire potion?
Hold on.
Let's get rid of pheromone.
Fire potion.
100% fire.
Well, don't drink it, that's for sure.
What do we have here?
Oh, not these guys.
This is a nightmare.
Holy fuck.
Actually nice to have a little outpost with these legs just to sit here, you know, and chill.
You don't have to think too hard about the movement.
I hit it, I hit it, I hit it.
Oh, I'm so dead.
T.
Oh, never mind, we're fine.
There's a wand there as well.
You know what?
We should go back.
9 HP, just ain't gonna cut it.
It's time to leave.
Uh, oh, shit, there's an enemy there.
Ah, shit!
Don't go that way, don't go that way.
Uh, here?
It's too narrow!
Oh, it's not, it's not, it's not.
Nice.
Come on.
Fuck all of y'all.
Okay, that was a bad idea.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Dead end!
Nice!
Gotcha.
Find a portal!
Bro, you want some?
I'm gonna, he's gonna kill me, right?
He's gonna fucking kill me.
Just move, just move, just move.
Ah, shit!
Careful now, be careful.
Oh!
Oh wait, now we're back in this place.
We don't want that, we don't want that, we don't want that.
Nice.
Keep moving.
Oh, this is the wrong spot!
Where the hell was this portal?
I think somewhere over here.
Is this it?
Is this maybe it?
Gotta be down here.
Uh-oh!
Oh, fuck!
That's okay.
I didn't like those legs anyway.
Part of me is relieved.
We are never taking that again.
That is terrible.
Oh, wait a minute.
We have TNT!
I'm actually so relieved not to have those legs anymore.
I feel much better now.
But now I know.
Don't ever pick the legs.
Because the whole movement that you've been accustomed to is just out the window.
You know?
It's a bit odd.
Nice.
The hell?
Let the breathe went on for a long time there.
Got it!
Uh...
What is that?
Is that a bush?
Why did that just fall down?
Ah, whatever.
Let's go!
That's 25 HP in the pocket.
Oh, that's a shitty wand.
A slow shitty wand.
But I'll make do.
Okay, new rule.
We're gonna find...
No more new rules.
We're gonna have too many rules.
Let's just play safe.
And there's a big guy right there.
That's...
Perfect shot!
Fuck yeah!
That's how we do it.
This thing's gonna explode?
Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
This can catch fire, so I gotta be careful.
In fact, I'm just gonna wait.
Water potion?
That's good to know.
Because that means if I catch fire, I can just quickly douse myself.
In fact, I kinda wanna blow it up.
Get rid of it.
Burn!
A wand right there!
Okay, we're gonna wait a bit for that fire to subside.
Chaotic party molt, I like it.
The hell is this?
What is this supposed to represent, even?
What kind of bowl?
Empty potion?
Wow!
That's the first time I've seen that.
Nice!
That's good!
Much better.
Now we're talking.
There's a wand here.
Hey, miss!
Oof!
They can be dangerous.
Circle of thunder.
A field of electrifying magic.
So this is a static projectile.
That scares me.
Because that means it's gonna appear right where I stand.
And I'm not about that.
I'm scared here.
Okay, nice, we can hide behind that.
Good!
Gave me the money.
Why did I just hear a loud roar?
There's a loud roar in the distance.
Oh, these are like vats, like barrel type deals.
There's oil in this one.
Some of them are empty.
Is that a fiery man?
What just descended?
No, it's a shoddy man.
Let me take care of this guy first.
Whew.
Close.
Ha!
Dutch!
I'm in a bad position here.
Oh!
Nice.
So far, so good.
I'm happy.
Got a hammus.
My god.
Nice.
Oh, that's a flaming skull.
I think he died.
Uh oh.
These guys are actually pretty dangerous.
I keep thinking this guy's alive.
We gotta murder him even more.
There we go.
Alright.
Man, I gotta get out of these mines, man.
I wanna get back to the snowy place.
You know, but I just need to have a good start here.
That's what it's all about.
Yeah, go this way first.
Let me keep up here.
And there's nothing.
Good.
I think this is the... yep, lava place.
Sick shot.
What do I have on me?
I have Chaotic Polymorphine and Water.
If I find Invisiblium or Acceleration or something like that, I'm gonna go there.
Although I have 100 HP, maybe I can survive the boss.
And escape it.
Give me money.
91 gold only.
We need more for sure.
Give me lots of Bloodstains.
Give me that crit.
Invis.
Cool.
What's that?
Polymorphine.
I think I just crit him.
Nice.
I'm playing well so far in this run here.
Oh, that was sick.
Nice.
Another portal there.
It's good to know.
Also, I do have 10 TNTs left.
So I can potentially get in anywhere.
Almost anywhere.
That is pheromone.
You know what?
Pheromone is actually not bad.
Because you can put it on the enemies, and they will become your friends.
Ah, no!
I panic when these guys get too close.
There we go.
Only lost 7 HP.
It's not too bad.
I wonder if I can pheromone the boss.
Make him my friend.
That would be pretty cool.
What do we have up here?
It's that thing again.
Oh, you know what?
I'm taking it.
Yes.
I'm going to put this rock on the altar near the boss.
And if that doesn't do anything, I'm going to throw it in the boss's face.
See what happens then.
I probably will just anger him.
That's fine, because I intend to escape if that happens.
You know, just throw a rock at someone, and if they get angry, you run.
Solid advice.
Okay.
Come on now.
Nice.
I'm not taking that gold.
A powder of brass!
Ah, let's get rid of the chaotic polymorphine, I guess.
I don't know why I'm taking this.
I feel like it's got to be important.
You know?
Oh wait, am I using...
No, I'm going to use this a bit.
I like this one.
Not bad.
It's decent.
So what do we have here?
Burning trail and fireballs.
Firebolts.
It's a shuffle.
We don't like that.
But this is also... wait, this is a circle of thunder.
I don't know.
Leave it.
I don't want it!
Maybe someone else will want it.
Not me.
Flammoxium.
Guess I go down.
Ooh, a chest!
I wand!
Holy shit, there's a bunch of stuff on this one!
Energy sphere, bouncing burst, luminous drill with timer.
I think I had one of these before and I didn't quite understand it.
Sparkables, another luminous home-bringer teleport bolt.
A bunch of stuff!
I think I want it just because it's a bunch of stuff.
Um, maybe I replace this one.
Yeah, fuck it.
And then we use this one as our main damage dealer.
Yeah, I do like the arrow.
We can probably make something out of that wand later.
Or the spells within it.
Don't even dare, sir.
Come here.
Headshot!
Sometimes these guys die with one arrow, sometimes they don't.
I don't understand.
And it doesn't specify a crit, so that's not what happens.
Wait, fu- I'm confused.
Why?
Is there such a thing as headshot?
Hold on.
Shit!
My god, I can't hit anything.
See, I did five damage, then I did ten.
I don't understand.
Why is that happening?
Uh, okay, I'm gonna get in there.
Sweet.
Uh...
What does he have in his hand?
Oh, okay!
My dude is insane.
Has a lot of HP, too.
How are you not dead?
Good.
Oh, I almost got poisoned.
A bit risky.
Oh, another one of these guys!
That's for you, sir.
Holy shit!
Ah, I- I- Dammit.
I, uh... forgot about that.
Whoops!
That was a bummer.
Happens, though.
This guy has a wand!
No!
She's not allowed.
Fuck you.
What do you have?
Wow!
A bunch of these.
And the wand doesn't look too bad either, does it?
Except it's shuffled.
Maybe I'll replace it with- Oh wait, this is the exact same wand.
Look!
The stats are identical!
The fuck?
That's crazy.
Um...
Maybe I don't want this.
I feel like that could fuck me up.
But I am curious to see what this will do.
Ah, I'm gonna replace my dynamite, I think.
Yeah.
This wand does look sick.
Look how fast that shoots!
And the reason it shoots that fast is because...
it has a cast delay of .03.
But then again, these add a cast delay too.
Wait, projectile speed times 110?
Weird.
Okay.
Oh, it's a frog!
They're actually scary.
Oh!
Yeah, burning hell.
There you go.
Giving that money.
Much better.
Fuck you!
I'm not taking that gold.
Playing safe.
I'm kind of sad not taking this gold.
That thing's gonna explode, isn't it?
66 HP.
We can keep going for a bit.
Damn!
I did not expect that would blow!
I didn't even think I hit it!
Or thought it would hit it.
But it did.
Always assumed the worst, I guess.
Wait, there's something up there.
I wanna check it out.
How do I do this?
Oh, wait.
I threw away my TNT.
That's fine.
We can go through.
I have a lot of money.
This time we're not gonna forget to refresh.
The hell is that?
Oh, it's a rock.
Let's see here.
Before we look at this.
I'm gonna go over here.
And look at these.
Wait, what?
Don't open that.
Fungal colony.
Slime near you spontaneously turns into fungal creatures.
That sounds not good.
Trick grade.
4x instead of 2x gold is dropped when death is an accident.
I don't understand this one.
Wand experimenter.
Firing newly found and unmod...
You know what?
This one seems good.
I'm taking that.
We shall be experimenting with wands galore and it will heal us.
Because there's wands everywhere and I wonder how much it will heal.
Can't wait to find out.
This is small teleport bolt.
That moves you wherever it ends up flying.
That is a great one.
And then we have a triple...
I want scatter for sure.
Light, I don't know.
This one, definitely.
Spitter bolt.
Energy sphere.
Chain bolt, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
I buy everything!
Fucking buy the whole store.
Not bad at all.
Okay, so now that I have so many spark bolts...
I can probably do some crazy shit, right?
Let me see here.
0.22, 0.03.
Let's try this.
Maximum spark.
Wait, is that all?
Why is it not even that fast?
I guess it adds 0.05 cast delay inherently there.
Simultaneously cast three spells.
That's better, I think.
I like it.
Then we have the chain bolt.
Oh, you know what?
No, no, man.
Now, this one is actually pretty nice.
It does 25 damage.
But it adds 0.75 cast.
Not that it matters, because it's only...
You know, for a one, using this, what I would like is a low recharge time.
That's what I really want.
Like this one.
Because...
I can shoot it more often, no?
No, this is faster.
How does that make sense?
This one has a lower recharge time?
And...
I mean, this one has a lower cast delay.
But that only matters when moving from one spell to the next.
And when this one is done firing, it starts a new sequence, right?
The hell?
Bop, bop, bop, bop, bop.
This one is definitely slower.
How does that make sense?
Maybe there is a simple cast delay at the end before it hits the recharge time.
Maybe that's simply what it is.
Unfortunate, but looks like that's what's happening.
No, don't throw it away.
So put this here.
Add a bunch of this.
Hey, that's pretty nice.
I like it.
Oh, spinner bolt?
Wait a minute.
One of each?
Maybe a bit too chaotic, huh?
And it's not that accurate, look.
It's actually kind of shit.
I don't like the non-accuracy of it.
But we can do something else here.
Uh, how fast is this?
Bop, bop.
Ooh.
Ah, but wait, this is shuffle.
Shuffle bad.
Oh!
I like it.
That's nice.
If we do this now...
Huh.
Oh wait, it's shuffle, so it's like random, I guess.
Let me try this real quick.
Okay.
Yeah.
So, bop, bop, bop, bop.
And then it hits this one.
And then it's gonna cast bop, bop, bop.
And then it's done.
Sequence done.
We start over, recharge time.
Bop, bop, bop, bop.
Dot, dot, dot.
Yeah.
Okay, uh, then we have this one.
I'm gonna keep that on that.
I kind of like this, but I don't like that.
So this is gonna be a...
Oh, no, no, this one.
This is what I wanted.
We have this one.
And then we have this one.
Like a nice little machine gun.
That's nice.
I like it.
That's our primary.
And then we have all kinds of shit down here.
Luminous drill with timer.
A pinpointed short-ranged beam of concentrated light that casts another spell after a timer runs out.
So, luminous drill.
What do you mean?
I think I tried experimenting with this once, but I didn't quite get it.
Can I...
Oh, yeah, it's this one.
Luminous drill.
Shuffle.
Pinpointed.
Castelay minus 0.58.
And minus recharge time, too.
Wait a minute.
Wait, what?
Okay.
Hold on.
Bum-bum.
Oh, yeah, I guess it is a little lower.
But when I look at this...
It says... So the inherent castelay is 0.08, right?
So this... So all of these take it below zero, actually.
And it also reduces...
Re... Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, it uses a lot of mana, too.
30.
Oh, it's not actually that much.
Why is it doing that?
That's... I don't understand.
Wait a minute.
This one has 250 mana.
Wait.
These are being shot so quickly, you can't even...
Look.
You saw that?
Also, there's a timer on, of course.
So after a certain time...
It fires the next one.
But then they all sort of have the timer, so it's like...
Really messed up.
Look how... Oh, that's why it goes so far.
Look.
Because this one summons that one, summons that one.
So it's all in a line.
You see how far it goes?
Pretty cool.
So if I only hit it once...
Three.
So that means... I fire this...
After a certain amount of time, it triggers that.
Which, after a certain amount of time, will trigger that.
And then it's over.
No, but then it goes to two more.
I guess it... Hmm.
That's interesting.
The way that works.
I wonder if I can just use these for the flat stat adjustments.
So if I... Okay.
If I want to do this...
Is that gonna fucking... How's that gonna work?
Hey!
That is insane!
Wait up a minute here.
I can totally game the system.
Hold on.
If I use... Let me find a good example here.
Something that adds a lot of... Oh, I don't have a good example, I guess.
Oh, this one.
See, this one adds...
So I guess... I guess I could test this, but...
Each of these adds .17 Castellae, right?
Bum, bum, bum, bum.
Oh no, is it only .17 Castellae in between each?
So this is right now a point... Oh, I can't measure that shit.
See, that's the... Why is that the same?
Dum, dum, dum, dum.
Hmm.
It definitely... Hold on, am I imagining things?
It definitely changed, didn't it?
Wait, what?
Oh, wait a minute.
The timer is gonna trigger a spark bolt as well.
I didn't think about that.
Of course it's gonna... Oh, let me grab that.
Yeah.
What if I put this here?
I don't understand what's happening.
Okay, let me click one at a time.
One, two, three, four, five...
It was very brief.
But you can sort of see when it reaches that one.
This one triggered that one.
Is that better?
It definitely is better.
What if I add two of them?
Ho!
Hello?
It's basically constant.
I'm limited by mana now.
Oh, this one cost a lot of mana to... Oh, wait a minute.
It's a balance.
This one is definitely better than... Hell yeah.
Yo, that is fucking awesome.
Let me try the...
Wait a minute.
I should probably add that on...
A timer.
Let's do this.
Let's try this now.
Hopefully we won't kill ourselves.
Okay.
And that's just gonna electrify shit.
Right?
Okay.
So if enemies walk into that, they're gonna get a handful of...
Electrons moving through their body.
I like it.
I do.
Maybe I'll use that.
Let's see.
What else can I do?
Oh, hold on.
Let me try some stuff here.
What if I do that?
Oh, that's a mess.
That is a complete mess and I love it.
It's sad that this takes so much mana.
If I had an add mana right now...
You could maybe make this go forever.
You know, make it a brrrr machine gun.
Okay.
I definitely want this.
We need a want just for the teleport.
Let's use this one because it's shuffle.
That's fine.
Wait!
Ah, it's this one.
Almost fucked that up.
That would have been a disaster.
Good thing I caught it.
Then we have TNT.
We definitely need that.
And I think I maybe... We can put the light on here, I guess.
It's a projectile modifier, so that goes there.
Yeah, I like having the light.
That's cool.
What else can we do?
This one.
At the end of... Hold on.
So what if I...
Oh, hold on.
If I do this now, it's gonna shoot it... Oh, how do I get past this now?
I didn't think it's gonna stay!
What the hell?
Can I get rid of it?
Shit.
Can I go through this?
I guess we're gonna test on the way out.
This may have been a mistake.
Yeah, I'm not gonna use it.
I'll use this instead.
It disappeared.
Thank God.
Okay, I like it.
Let's go.
The symbol.
All right, cold pits time, baby.
We have a sick wand.
The hell is this?
Oh, it's a lamp that fell.
Okay.
Hey, rats.
Nice.
Bloody gunpowder.
There's nothing like it.
That's the end of the line.
I kind of want to blow this up.
Do what?
Oh, I don't really have anything that can do that.
The thing that's confusing me with this luminous drill...
Oh, wait!
I can dig with it now.
Okay, I think I understand.
Oh, but it's not a modifier, though.
It's a projectile.
I was about to say, I can put this on, let's say, TNT and it will dig more efficiently, but that's not how that works.
It's a spell on its own.
What's happening here?
What is this?
Invisibilium!
And flammoxium.
What?
That looked like a hand carrying a little ball.
Am I crazy?
Maybe I am.
God, I love this wand now.
It's a decent wand.
I enjoy.
Oh!
Almost ran out of levitation there.
Is that it?
No, it's just slime.
Sick.
Man, we found the portal already.
Ah, shit!
We're okay.
Right, we gotta try the newly found wand stuff.
But we gotta take damage first, I guess, but I'm not gonna take damage on purpose or anything.
No, no.
But the problem with that perk is, if I'm too good at the game, it's not gonna be useful.
Yeah, this is a decent wand.
Look how good it is.
And it's just a simple spell.
It just shoots fast.
Ah, that gold is not something I want.
I think I understand what's happening with the damage numbers now, by the way.
The reason it set five before and then ten is because if the damage is happening over a short enough time period, it gets added.
So it's just showing the total that I'm doing.
Look, that was total in fifteen.
Or in three shots or whatever.
Or like five shots, I guess?
They do three shots a pop, right?
So I understand.
That's what I'm saying.
Ah, let me go up here.
Is it a dead end?
Damn it.
I'm gonna dig.
Wait, I can dig.
Actually, nice.
Not really super advanced here.
Wait, can I not get through that?
Oh, this is... Man, this spell right here is so weird.
There's something I'm not getting about it.
I just don't understand it.
Speed 1400.
It's so weird.
Let me blow it up instead.
I need to understand that spell.
At some point.
Same with the chainsaw.
Like, I know it adds speed, but it's also a short-range weapon that cuts meat.
It's honestly similar to the luminous drill in that it just increases the attack speed.
Of my spells.
But it's like, it's also a drill.
You know, it's like a function on another function.
So the drill gives you speed and it also gives you a drill function.
But the chainsaw gives you speed.
And it gives you the option to chainsaw enemies, I guess.
But I feel like that would be a terrible idea.
Maybe it does a sick amount of damage.
I actually never tried it on an enemy.
Maybe with invisibility you could do some damage with that.
Get up close and do a...
Do I want to go through?
Not yet.
I need a bit more money at least.
I mean, I'm at 131 HP.
We have some room here to maneuver.
Let's go left.
Bap, bap, bap.
Oh, shicers.
That was crazy.
A chest!
Oh, sick!
I love that.
Hell yeah.
Gold problems be gone.
See, but now I'm still greedy.
We still have 131 HP.
We should keep going.
Because, think about it like this.
If we get shitty perks, we can maybe even reroll twice.
And that's a big deal.
Perks are like... incredibly important.
If you get the right perks, things can change drastically.
Oh, we're back at the start.
Time to use some dynamite.
Yep.
Sweet.
Aw, man!
Okay, hold on.
Sick!
For the remainder, we can use this.
Yeah, that works.
Notice how when you shoot, you can actually see the green laser.
Go to about here.
And that's the drill.
So I can't actually dig from this distance.
It needs to be within that range.
Douse!
I get so panicky when I'm on fire.
Aw, mate, it pushes the gold into these cracks.
That's totally... not good.
I was like, oh, I can just use this to get some nice gold real quick.
He's gonna blow up this.
Ah, he's gonna die!
You idiot!
What are you doing?
Oh, but now I can't get the gold.
That was great.
It's okay.
Sick.
Yo, what the hell is this?
It's a wooden wall on fire.
Let me in.
I shall enter these premises.
Rats.
There's a wand.
We can test the healing.
Oh, another wand!
Oh, sick!
Ah, the fungal caverns.
What the hell is that?
Linear arc makes a projectile fly only in cardinal or diagonal lines.
Interesting.
I mean...
It has a bunch of spark bolts.
I kind of want to replace this dynamite.
We can come back for it.
Okay, so we have to shoot it.
It fucking healed me.
I don't... I got full health.
I don't know how much I had.
But I was definitely not at full health.
Uh-oh.
This guy has a lot of HP.
Damn!
That was a violent explosion.
More violent than usual, I would say.
Let's light that up.
Oh, we can't.
Whoop!
Didn't mean to do that.
Wrong wand.
I kind of forgot I had that wand.
So I do want to grab the other wand up here.
And I got to go into this area, man.
I have to master these fungal areas.
Oh, that's scary.
Maybe I don't have to master these.
What the hell are you?
It's like a floating piece of metal.
What is this?
Oh, no, not this.
Stay in me.
Shit!
Oh, it's already chaos.
Oh, God, it's above.
This place is hell.
It's in there.
Oh, shit!
Fuck off.
Okay, if we get below 50% or like 50 HP, we're leaving.
That's the rule.
We can stay until then.
Now...
I should use this, actually.
Okay.
The wand is right above me somewhere.
So if I can get in there.
And there's...
What the hell is that?
Oh, God, there's robots.
Robots, these guys are scary.
I feel like I shouldn't be here.
Is this a mistake?
I want that.
What?
We're going, we're going.
Okay.
Dig, dig.
Get out of here.
Let me dig in peace.
Can I get in?
I have to wait a bit.
Come on.
Yes!
Oh!
Double spell.
Fire trail.
Sparkly bounce.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know.
Maybe I'll replace it with this one.
Yeah, I'll take it.
Let's go a little further.
I have a problem.
I know!
I have a problem!
Uh...
Levitation!
That's good, though.
Get rid of the worm shit.
There's a robot.
Got it.
Hold on.
Let's...
Let's pheromone him.
Wait, does that work on mechanical entities?
Sir?
It does not.
Okay.
How do I deal with this guy?
Also, I should fire this one, so I get HP.
Hey!
It's a sick heal!
Wait, it keeps healing me?
No way!
I can spam it?
There's no fucking way.
Also, these are fire because fire trail.
Huh.
That's nuts!
How is that not broken as fuck?
Ah, see ya.
Kinda want to get past here, but what is that burning?
Oh, it's a fungus on fire.
Burn it a little faster, fungus.
Got rid of him.
Ah, that's scary.
The hell is that?
Slimy egg.
Interesting.
Let's get rid of the brass pouch.
I don't know what it's for yet.
B!
I want this.
The egg is covered in slime.
Maybe if you get an egg with each element or whatever, and put them somewhere, something will happen.
Uh oh, uh oh.
I have to remember, I have this wand.
It's a good wand.
Oh, this is a nice spot.
Money!
Come here, come here.
I'm playing this super patient and slow.
Just the way I like it.
Bup!
Bada!
I healed again!
Even though I didn't need it.
Hell yeah, see ya.
We see it's broken.
Uh, what the hell is going on there?
Oh, he's shooting that bullshit that makes me blind.
Don't like that.
Can I pheromone him?
I threw away the, no I didn't.
Pheromone!
You are my friend!
Okay, maybe not.
He is not.
Got him!
Huh?
Oh no, it was teleportation!
I'm fucked!
Okay, be ready.
It's soon over, it's soon over.
It's over.
And he's my friend now.
Teleportation, man.
That is, whoa!
Someone has a wand.
Hello!
I have a wand too.
Where'd you go?
Yep, yep, yep.
Come on, bring it on.
This is a mess.
But I love it.
Shit!
If I shoot it again.
It still heals me!
This is crazy!
That perk is nuts!
Uh, I'm gonna wait.
There we go.
Where did that fire?
Man, these little enemies here are actually the worst.
I can't even reach that guy.
He's there, I see him.
Hold on.
Uh, maybe if I use...
Oh.
Shit.
Got him.
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
Come on.
Man, they each dropped money though, that's actually nuts.
Oh, they don't, nevermind.
Yeah, they do!
Uh oh, uh oh.
Fuck!
What's that?
Book of Guidance?
What?
Hold on.
I gotta find that again.
Book of Guidance?
I am not leaving this place until I find that.
I'm telling you that right now.
Is that healing me?
Maybe not anymore.
Oh, shit.
I'm burning.
Hold on, I also have this one.
That's healing me now.
Maybe it heals a little bit less every time you use it.
But it's still insane.
Act absolutely bonkers.
This is what it is.
Get bloody.
Get the crits.
Fuck off.
Oh, we've got a ghostbuster and a wand in there.
Oh wait, yeah, that is a wand.
Shit, oh shit.
Nice.
Man, this wand is solid.
I have a lot of money.
Uh, how do I get in there?
Probably with the, with the acid, right?
Can I not get in there?
Can I not?
Okay, that's a bit nuts.
Shit.
I have to get in through the bottom, I think.
Or find something explosive.
Another, wow.
Oh, what the hell is that?
It spawns these guys.
Some kind of bee.
Hosh!
Jesus!
Okay.
Heal me.
Man, the healing has come in clutch.
Ah.
Ah, fuck.
Kill it!
Oh, thank God.
We gotta kill that.
I'm out of mana.
No wait, I'm out, yeah, I'm out of mana.
Man, I'm in a stupid position here.
There, got it.
It fell down?
Okay, they don't drop money, these guys, when you kill them.
That's interesting.
Is that gold?
It's honey.
Wow.
Eat it.
The nice thing about this wand against these guys is that I can spam it and it will just kill the projectiles they shoot at me automatically.
It's awesome.
What's this?
Berserkium.
I like Berserkium.
So to get in here, I need to go through here.
I could do it with this, it's gonna take a while though.
Yeah.
Oh, I can just stand here and do that.
I mean, I have to get in there.
If I can make a little crack, I can teleport in there with my wand.
That's all I need to do.
Is that lava coming?
Yes!
I did it!
Okay, what's this?
Damage plus.
And a bunch of fire bolts.
Minus 12 degrees spread, huh?
So I wonder if this means that if I put in a scatter spell, something that spreads projectiles a lot.
If this will like focus it more.
Let's say I could have a scatter of three.
Maybe I can have enough minus degrees of spread to actually make it back into a straight line.
You know, that could be cool.
In any case, I'm gonna replace this because now I can start healing again, no?
Wait, what?
Wait, is that...
Oh, never mind.
I thought this was cutting through the material.
So to get in here, I'm gonna do the same.
Also, let me shoot this new spell.
Full HP again.
In fact, I should wait shooting that until I lost more HP because it's less HP heal every time.
Let's get in here.
Dude, this is so fucking fun.
I love this game.
Like every run is so unique.
There's always some crazy shit happening.
Wait, why can't I get in there?
Why is that not working?
I'm hitting.
Say what?
Maybe there's not enough room.
Wait, what?
Why is that not working?
I'm going nuts.
This will just cut my way in.
That should be enough, right?
No, not quite.
Almost.
There we go.
Aha!
A triplicate bolt.
Ah shit, I don't know what to replace though.
Maybe this one, because it's already been, honestly, these things on here are not that enticing to me.
I don't really care about them that much.
Maybe the double spell is the only one that I really like here.
The rest?
Nah, not really.
And by this, by taking this, I can start healing again with this wand.
I'm not going to shoot it yet.
Because I need to, I need it for the healing.
I need to find that book of knowledge or whatever it was called.
Book of guidance?
Now that is intriguing.
A book of guidance.
What?
I need me some of that.
Okay, are we at the very bottom then, because this dense rock is here?
A chest!
Fuck yeah.
What's in it?
Oh, it's invisibilium potion.
Ah, okay, okay.
Um, I mean...
Ah, you know what, I...
I'm going to keep the egg.
Pheromone?
Fuck off.
Actually...
Yeah, I don't want pheromone, but I do want invisibilium.
That can come in handy.
It can actually come in real handy.
Someone's in there.
Let me go up first.
Things have calmed down a little bit in here.
This fungal grove has been pure chaos for the longest time, but now it's sort of calming down a little bit.
We have a dude there.
Okay, weird fungus.
Maybe that gold.
I hate these enemies so much.
I would love the electricity bomb against these guys.
Something explodey, you know?
The hell?
Oh, it's one of those guys.
Fuck you!
You're still alive.
Thank you.
I can... I should heal... No, I'm going to wait a bit and then heal when I lost more HP.
Oh, whoa, whoa!
Wait, are these the same legs I grew in the other run?
They have the same... Oh, there we go.
He died fast.
Sweet.
Got him.
I do want to kill this guy over here, but he is hard to kill.
Maybe they have a weakness.
Probably electricity, if you think about it.
They're made of metal, right?
Electricity would fuck up their circuits.
Just overcharge him.
Are you going to be able to hit me from here?
Get cheesed, bitch!
Yeah!
Oh, that's great.
And now I need that money.
That's oil.
That's a little bit dangerous.
Thank you.
Is this back at the start?
I think it is.
Oh, this little fucker.
Got him.
That sound I'm hearing?
Is that the sound of teleportation liquid?
It sounds like something like a little wispy, doesn't it?
God, these enemies are just the worst.
They may be my least favorite enemies in the game so far.
They are so annoying.
Especially with this wand, you know?
Maybe they wouldn't be as annoying with another wand.
But you have to be very precise to hit them with this wand.
We've got a big frog.
So much HP.
God damn it.
Give me that money.
That's a bit risky for me.
What is that?
Invisiblium.
I have that already.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, that's a wand I've already done.
Up.
Hello.
This is a mess.
I can't hit anything.
I'm dying to these guys.
Kill them.
Oh, it's leaking invisiblium.
I wonder if that's making the enemies invisible.
Okay, I'm going to shoot the experimental wands now.
Oh yeah, it still heals.
Nice.
And that's it.
Cool.
And then I can heal with the next wand when I need it.
I'm going to lose a bit more HP first.
What's this?
Oh, it's a fire potion.
Ah!
Didn't see you there!
You bastard!
Alright, now we can shoot this wand.
Actually a cool looking shot.
I like it.
I have another wand!
I love this perk so much.
In fact, this should do good damage, no?
Whoa!
Why did I get teleported?
What the hell?
Wait, is he alive?
He was alive!
There's a chest.
What did I get?
Did I get this potion?
Wait, my screen is all wobbly.
What the hell?
Why was my screen wobbly?
Okay, what do we got?
Reduce spread!
Oh!
Hello!
That's exactly the thing I was looking for.
Because if I combine that with stuff like this, it's pretty cool.
This is a crazy wand.
Long recharge time though, but a lot of mana max.
I don't know yet.
Maybe I will leave it for now.
And come back when I've exhausted this one of healing.
That's my plan.
This is basically healing, sitting right here.
It's awesome.
Bro, I am clearing this place.
Oh, there's a guy there.
You know what?
Eh!
Okay, he shoots.
He's gonna catch fire.
Oh, I'm gonna catch fire.
I'm not careful.
You can't hit me.
You suck.
Let me hit him with this one.
Oh, okay.
Man, this guy is killing me.
He died, he died, he died.
Everything is right in the world.
All that gold though?
That's fine, I have 1100 right now.
I don't care about that gold.
We care about the book.
That's all I care about.
Bro, there we go.
Where could it be?
I only have a glimpse, like a very small memory where I glimpsed it.
Brass, brass plus, oh, I've been here already, yeah.
So keep going left now.
Maybe it's over here.
Oh, we've got some toxic rock.
I wonder what these guys are called.
Can I see them in here now?
These little fuckers.
Where are you?
Moikki, Moikki.
Kyoko Moikki.
I hate them.
Moikki sucks.
Come here, Moikki.
You little Moikki?
Come on, die.
There it is.
I have found it.
He teleported because he's in...
Teleportation!
Oh, it, oh.
One of my brethren ran away in order to escape our predicament.
They felt our understanding of this world was to be forbidden.
They hid something here in this room, but...
I lack the ability to truly see what is here.
What?
Am I, is there something here that I'm not seeing right now?
They hid something here in this room?
Wait, can I take that with me?
Let's get rid of this egg.
I don't like it anymore.
Hoo!
Oh, they're my friends.
You're friends, right?
Yeah, nice, cool.
I got it.
How, so in this room, I do notice that it's on this sort of...
triangular piece of brickwork.
Something is hidden in plain sight, huh?
Something I can't see.
Maybe I need to be affected by a certain debuff to be able to see something.
Maybe if I use the all-seeing eye spell here, something would happen.
That's levitation?
What the hell's going on there?
Someone's shooting something very luminous.
I kind of want to try and blow this up right here.
I don't have anything to blow up, though.
Dammit.
Hamus?
Are those Hamus eyes?
Oh, it's a ghostbuster.
Got him.
Oh, we got one of those guys.
They're dangerous.
Come on, little helpers.
Kill him.
You're useless.
Also, I don't like the levitation right now.
It's fucking up my movement.
What do we have up here?
Loops around.
Cool.
Oh, fuck this guy.
I got him!
Nice.
Double scatters.
I don't like it.
Oh, wait.
Does this count?
Wait a minute.
We got a test.
If I now change this for that for a second...
and I shoot it...
Oh, fuck.
There we go.
Does this count as healing now?
Which one was it?
This one.
Get out of the way.
Oh, it totally does!
That's sick!
Oh, we're gonna... This is the best perk of all time.
This is just incredible.
Fuck.
I don't...
I don't wanna...
Okay.
Here's the plan.
I'm gonna go over here.
Can I just drop it like that?
Oh, no!
Not down there!
We gotta get in there.
Got it.
Okay.
I'm gonna leave this here...
and I'll come back for it later.
If I need some healing, I know where it is.
I say that, but I really don't.
It's somewhere in here along the left wall.
That's what I have to remember.
Empty potion there.
I think that's the one I shot.
Unstable teleportation potion?
Excuse me?
What do you mean, unstable?
I'm intrigued.
Oh, man.
I wanna throw something away.
I don't know.
I don't know what to think.
Maybe the levitation...
You know what?
The invisibilium can go away.
Bleh!
I want this.
In my direst moments, I will use it.
When everything is bleak, and I have no hope, I shall drink this potion...
and everything will be alright with the world.
Hopefully things won't go that far.
Oh, we'll see.
Blood me up.
Alright.
Oh, there's an enemy.
Wait!
What are you shooting?
I wonder if I can take damage from those projectiles.
Okay, so, honey.
Right, there was this whole area.
I didn't explore that yet.
Let's go!
Holy shit!
Okay, okay, calm down.
Let's heal a bit.
What the hell is this?
Water?
Pheromone and...
Oil.
Nope!
Wait, what is that?
That's a weird sound.
Why is it making that sound?
Whoa!
The teleportation wand is crazy.
Oh, he's a friend.
I hope he died.
Did I just pick up some gold?
Yeah, what's going on up there?
Let me through.
Man, this place is huge.
Oh, wait, I've been here.
Never mind.
Back down we go.
Okay, now we're back in the normal caverns then.
I think it's time to go through.
Oh, look at all the gold.
Ah, there we go.
It's time.
Let's-a go.
Man, that was a crazy session there.
Fuck yeah, almost full HP, huh?
Doesn't get better than that.
And we have wands to choose from, okay.
What do we have here?
A double and some stuff?
Wow.
A bunch of spark bolts.
And always cast something.
That's right, they also have that sometimes.
This is the drunkenness.
And more spark bolts and a light.
Let's see if the wands have any good stats.
Basically I'm looking for low numbers of cast delay and recharge time.
Okay.
Let's see here.
So we have this one.
Projectile modifier, it adds 10 damage.
Now hear me out.
On the spark bolt.
If we-oh, wait a minute.
Is that only gonna modify...
one of them?
Wait.
Ah, fuck.
I thought I could put the-but wait, I can.
Oh, watch.
Oh, dude, dude, dude, dude.
Triple scatter?
No, I thought I picked up something that reduced scatter.
I didn't take it with me.
Crap.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
Fuck.
Damn it.
But this is also-this should work on all of them.
Yeah, look, look, look.
You can see the effect on it.
Not bad at all.
So if I can...
So this one has spread two, right?
Spread two minus 12.
What if we put it all here?
Let's see.
Oops.
Come on, I'm scared.
Jump in the water now.
I have nightmares of jumping into this water.
If I now do this down here instead...
It adds 20 degrees of spread.
This minimizes minus 12.
So that's actually not bad.
Hey, that's pretty cool.
Except it shoots quite slow.
You know?
But then again...
If you shoot these, and they all have...
Dude, that's an insane amount of damage.
Like, right there.
It's not that fast, though.
Wait, you can see the damage here.
Oh, so if you hit these...
Wait, why is it 30?
Okay, that's awesome.
I didn't know that.
Is that what happened last time when I could see the damage when I was throwing the egg?
Was I hitting something over here?
Wait a minute.
What was I hitting over here?
Oh, perks!
I forgot about these.
Hold on.
Revenge explosion.
You release a magical explosion upon taking damage.
And gain 25% resistance.
Nah, that's...
Nah, I don't know.
I don't like that.
More love.
Creatures become more friendly towards...
No, I don't like that.
Feared by worms.
Worms run away from you?
No, I don't want that either.
I'm just gonna re-roll that.
Bloink!
Loki minion.
And Loki...
No, I don't like that.
Gamble one off.
You gain two random perks.
Oh, that's...
That is a gamble, isn't it?
Oh, I'm tempted.
But this could ruin things.
If I'm not careful.
I'm not gonna do it.
I'm gonna re-roll.
Fuck it.
Pinpointer.
Your spells fly faster and have lower spread!
And you have a handy sight line for aiming.
Oh, this is the one I had before.
I had this one once.
Concentrated spells.
Your spells have lower spread, again.
And extra damage, but have increased cast delay.
Okay.
Critical hit plus.
You get more critical hits.
How much more are we talking?
That's what I wanna know.
I feel like this is...
This is great.
Let's see how much lower.
Oh, it's pretty much eliminated.
There's no spread.
Look!
That is a straight fucking line.
Oh, yeah, baby.
That's awesome.
Hold on.
Yeah.
Dude.
If I can make this shoot faster.
Wait!
Oh, dude!
Wait, uh...
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
Let me think.
What am I limited by?
I'm limited by recharge, right?
Definitely.
So, recharge...
minus point seven.
What if I add this here?
What happens then?
Oh!
It doesn't...
It does need to be inside the triple scatter.
What if it is, though?
Okay.
What if I just change it up a bit?
Okay, that's weird.
What?
Wait.
How does that work?
Hold on.
Why is that so fast?
Excuse me?
Okay, so it adds damage here.
And it adds the damage to...
Oh, but wait a minute.
Oh, we can see it here.
So, it shoots triple...
What is the one in between?
That one.
What if I do this?
So, it shoots triple...
Okay, let me see if I understand this.
This, right here, the only purpose this has...
is to reduce recharge time.
And cast delay, I guess.
And then it hits...
So, it shoots this.
This is a projectile.
Bam.
It's shot.
But, it's off.
But apparently, it also affects everything else.
So, this is like something that modifies the stats on the wand.
Not the next spell.
This modifies the stats of the wand.
So, in total, every one of these gets this buff, right?
So, it shoots this projectile.
Boom.
It shoots it off.
Then it hits the projectile modifier, which then modifies...
this spark bolt...
to have 10 extra damage.
But then...
Okay, so, these are not affected by the plus damage.
Right?
Because this only affects that one.
Now it affects all three, but it shoots slower.
And the reason it shoots slower...
Listen to this.
If I put it here...
Hold on, is this actually... No, no.
So, if I put it, it's like this, that, and it starts over.
Because it needs one more.
So, is it getting the double buff from this?
Is that what's happening?
The issue is, we don't have enough mana anyway?
But the problem is, the double damage here is not actually affecting what I wanted...
Oh, we can do this, though.
That way, I have more damage on two of them instead of one.
Hold on.
I can test this.
Let me go over here.
Let me notice the damage numbers.
32... 32... 32... 32...
Oh, it's always 32!
It's just because when I spam it, it adds sometimes, you know?
And we get the full damage.
So, it's 32...
Wait, what?
32...
Wait, why is that still 32?
Ah,
man.
So, this...
Does this affect everything, then?
No, projectile modifier should only affect this one, though.
So, that would be 13... plus...
Oh!
It's shooting this one twice!
No, wait, is it... Hold on.
Let me do this.
39...
32...
Yeah.
Okay, so it seems like...
It shoots this one.
That's one spell.
Modifier, it shoots this one.
Those are two spells cast.
Done.
Then it goes to the third spell, and the third spell is this triple scatter, which contains...
One, two, three spells.
Right?
But this one doesn't have the damage buff.
So, this should do...
13...
Plus...
3...
Plus 3...
Right?
So, 19...
And then...
It shoots this one.
Oh, but this one does 10 damage!
Oh, wait, was I... Hold on.
Let me just quickly see that.
If I go here...
I cut it in half.
Whoops.
I'm sorry.
No, okay.
No, no, no.
So, it takes that one, that one...
But why... I don't understand how this is 32 damage!
I don't get that!
I don't get it.
The only way that would... So, it doesn't even make sense that it applies it to all of them.
Because that would be 13 plus 13 plus 13.
Which is 39.
So, that makes sense.
Seeing... Oh, I can't even see it anymore.
I broke the thing.
Well, okay.
Whatever.
But, here's the thing.
When I shoot all these three...
It's 39.
That makes sense to me.
How is this 32?
Doesn't matter.
It shoots fast, right?
Then again, this is more... I think I like this more, even though it shoots slower.
It's more damage per blast.
And you don't want to blast that often anyway.
So, anyway, I started blasting, right?
Okay, I'm good with that.
I'm fucking good with that.
Unless... Let me see this again.
Yeah, it's a bit too slow.
Can I add this at the end?
Hold on.
Let me just play around with this.
Wait, is that faster?
No, it's not.
Okay.
What if I just add it randomly like this?
Oh, that's weird.
It shoots... Yeah, okay.
It's shooting that one and then it does the next.
And then it shoots that one, next, that one, next.
Okay, it alternates.
Oh, I should be looking at this more.
Holy shit.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm an idiot.
Why didn't I just look at that?
And then I can maybe understand what's going on.
So, the first one does... I wish this would stay on the board a bit longer.
So, it shoots... Scatter two of those.
That one.
And extra damage on that.
Oh, I think I, I think I... Oh, I understand.
I get it now.
I get it.
I understand.
It's a timer.
So, basically what's happening... It shoots this one first.
But what does that do?
It triggers the next spell.
Which is this one, right?
So, that's 13 damage.
Then it shoots this spell, which is that spell without damage plus.
That spell without damage plus.
And that one.
But that one triggers the next spell with another 13.
So, that's 26 plus, I guess, 6, which is 32.
Hallelujah.
The math checks out.
God damn, I understand.
Wait a minute.
Can I still not do this?
Show me damage.
Oh, I'm out of mana.
I understand how it works.
Fuck yeah.
Whoops.
That's all I needed to know.
Now I'm happy.
So, what I'm going to do now is actually go back to this configuration.
I like it being a little slower, but more controlled.
And that I don't run out of mana suddenly.
I like that.
Okay.
Oh, but wait.
We also have this stuff.
We have double there.
We actually have... Oh, man.
We have all kinds of things to play with.
Hallelujah.
Aghtulhibaugustus.
Aghtulhibaugustus, alles ist veg.
Buy it.
Replace it with... Hold on, will this... do that?
And then...
This one we will... Oh, dude.
I'm not done.
I'm not fucking done.
We're gonna...
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Wait!
Let me see if that's a good want!
This one has 0.18, 0.53...
Well dude, we're not done.
One... Ah!
This one could be... Oh wait, but I'm looking for the minus degree in scatter.
Unless the pinpointer... I wonder how much scatter reduction that actually gives.
You know?
That's the big deal here.
I guess I can just test it.
Let me put this up here.
Uh, don't want any of these right now.
I'm gonna take this.
There.
Oh dude.
I completely forgot that I had more wants!
Uh, yeah.
Now we're gonna do... Oh dude.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let me see if I get this right.
Let's just test it.
No, no, I'm gonna predict.
Okay, so... It shoots a double spell.
What is the first spell?
This one.
That triggers the next spell, which is what?
Right?
And that's all these.
So this is actually only one spell so far.
So that means this one is still not done.
So it needs another one.
What is the next one?
It is actually itself.
So what does that mean?
I actually don't know.
Let's see.
Wait, what?
Okay.
Wait, I can see... Let's look up here.
Okay, so it's not actually doing what I thought.
Let me go back to this.
So it's doing...
Okay.
Hmm.
What if I instead add this at the end?
Huh.
Okay.
Oh, wait a minute.
Maybe I do it like this instead.
That's what happens then.
Okay.
All right.
Here.
Oh, that's... Oh, that some fucked up wonky shit is happening there.
I don't even want to try and understand this right now.
Okay, so...
Fuck with the double spell.
We're not gonna fuck with that right now.
I feel like we had a good wand here.
This is a good wand.
There.
Uh, no, it was this one, wasn't it?
Whoops.
Yep.
There.
That is a decent wand.
I'm not gonna... That is... That's a good wand.
That's a good wand.
Oh, but wait a minute.
0.03.
Oh, this is shuffled though.
We don't want that.
Okay.
Is there anything else I want here?
I could go for... Oh, I don't have any money left.
Nevermind.
We're out of money.
No more money.
Okay.
I feel like I could do something with this.
You know, something smart.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's fine.
Black hole though.
Yeah.
Maybe I do like that more.
I could just click like this if I need control, right?
I don't need to go crazy.
Yeah, I like this more.
Okay.
This is still gonna be my teleportation wand.
Sure.
This one is fine.
I think I do kind of like that.
What if I do double teleport?
What happens then?
Wait a minute.
I guess not much, right?
Why would I... Oh, wait.
I need two spells anyway for that to work.
Whoops.
What if I break the game?
Bring the target hit closer to you.
Does that mean we meet in the middle?
Oh, that's funny.
Whoops.
Didn't mean to take that.
All right.
Well, that's fine.
Not that I am using any spells anyway.
Everything's fine.
Get rid of that.
I want to get rid of some of these.
I don't like these.
Get them off my bar.
This is a good wand.
Put this up here.
I want to keep this.
So this one is gonna be my... So what is this even?
Do I want it like that?
Maybe I put that there.
Okay.
Teleport wand.
Check.
We have our damage wand.
We have a firebolt wand.
Sure.
Why not?
I think we're good.
Cool.
Let's rock and roll, baby.
We're off on a grand adventure.
Cool.
That's a sick wand.
I'm proud of it.
We are back.
Oh, and a very cold welcome already.
Oh, we've got electricity, boys.
And they're working.
They're doing their thing.
Oh, god.
Where are you?
Wow, what a hit!
Damn.
Wait, does this guy kill himself?
Okay.
I do like this laser pointer.
I already lost a bunch of HP.
This is not a good start.
We need to find new wands and try them so we can heal.
Yo, this wand does sick damage.
Are you kidding?
This is sick.
This is a great wand.
The song that's playing right now is my favorite in this game so far.
Got it.
Heck yeah.
Let's wait for this to go away.
This is the run, boys.
And girls.
Ah, took damage.
We're fine.
This is the one where I discover insane.
Oh, man, it's so good.
It's like a boom.
We got a wand.
Got him.
It's such a fast projectile weapon that does so much.
It's actually amazing.
It's pretty much a laser.
Fine.
There is a laser pointer, but you know.
You know what I mean?
How do I get in there?
Probably this one.
Oh, come on.
Yeah, baby.
Oh, someone's in there.
Be careful.
Wait for them to come out.
Play it safe.
Money.
Fill me with blood.
Oh, yeah, look at that.
Completely submerged.
Oh, shit.
Okay, those guys still need a lot of damage.
Before they... Oh, my God.
I'm low on HP here.
Two wands.
Holy shit.
What the hell is this?
Electric charge.
Gives a projectile and electric charge that it will release on impact.
Nice.
I mean, cool.
I'll take it.
Let's heal.
Let's try it.
Look at the electric effect on them.
And I'm full health.
In fact, I'll carry this around for a bit.
No, I'll switch it back.
I can come back later.
The healing on this is insane.
The fact that I can just do that is mind blowing.
Let's get rid of these projectiles.
Shit.
Now we're making our way in there.
What do we got?
Oh, all kinds of new things.
A slow but powerful orb of energy.
Poison arc creates arcs of poison between two projectiles.
Oh, okay.
Triple spell, baby.
There's some good stuff in here.
Okay, I'll leave this here for now.
I'll come back and heal later.
Let's see what we have.
I'm going to go right first.
Haha.
I feel so safe with the healing on the wands.
It's crazy good.
That has to be one of the best perks I've ever taken.
Another wand!
Damn.
A bunch of acid balls.
All right.
That's another healing option there.
Do I need it?
What's next?
I want to go this way.
There's a hand.
Holy shit!
Wait, I did this exact thing last time as well, didn't I?
I have flashbacks too.
I have deja vu right now.
Holy crap, dude.
I've done that exact same thing before.
Another... Oh shit, we've got one of those electric boys.
Fuck you.
Oh, he's dead.
I killed him.
That was sweet.
Get rid of that.
Quadruple scatter spell?
Say what?
That's nuts.
Another heal.
Another wand over.
Bro, the wands are everywhere.
I love it.
Drain that shit.
What's this?
Concentrated light.
It does damage.
Two quadruple?
The fuck?
I'll try it.
No, not yet.
I need to take more damage.
This is insane.
This is wild.
Did you see that?
Am I crazy or did the thing just move?
You can actually just shoot them.
I just had Dark Souls flashbacks there as well for a moment.
I don't want to reveal too much if you haven't played Dark Souls, but...
Those that know know is all I'm going to say.
But that looked a little scary there.
What's this?
Meat.
I eat it.
I'm almost empty.
I don't understand the satiation system.
I don't get it.
Another wand.
The fuck?
Oh wait, this is...
It's a trap.
Shit.
Is that still connected?
Oh, I took damage.
Oh, it's spawning.
Come here.
Oh, let me blow that up.
That's a hazard for later.
Uh, yeah, I don't know if I should... I'm scared of lightning, man.
I've had experiences, okay?
Not good ones.
Pheromone potion.
Let me blow this up some more.
There we go.
Oh, fuck me.
That scared me.
All right.
Now, bunch of electric charge here.
The hell?
I mean, I'll take it and shoot it a couple of times.
Get some health.
Nice.
Take it back.
There's so much healing to be had here.
It's crazy.
There's the portal.
You got a spawner?
Oh, the effects on this one look so cinematic.
Just look at that.
Doesn't that look cool as hell?
And there's definitely a bunch of recoil on it too.
I don't know if you can tell, but when I shoot, it's like going like this.
I have to control it a little bit.
You see?
You can just feel the power in this wand.
Oh, shit.
My dude just headshot at me.
Something in here.
This is a hollow place.
Kind of want to get in there.
How do I get in there?
Dude, I know how to get in there.
Oh, what did I do?
That was so cool.
This game is amazing.
Now we can dig our way in like this.
Oh, man.
It's using mana quick.
That's the thing.
Hello.
Oh, thank you.
Piece of ice.
It broke the piece of ice.
I mean, the piece of ice broke the guy.
Get out of here.
I need gold.
Thank you.
Oh, I just took damage.
There's a guy up there.
Oh, that was a cool effect.
Did you see that?
When I broke the ice, it scattered like it had these, you know what I mean?
Like when you...
I don't know how to explain this in English.
You can see the pattern of the breaking happening.
That was so cool.
Thank you.
Another wand.
It's just showering with the ones.
This is wild.
Wait, why is that suddenly so good at digging?
Let's wait a bit.
Dude, if I can find an add mana spell, that would do everything.
Oh, wait, this is...
Oh, wait, this is the same wand I found earlier.
Oh, I came from the other side now.
Cool.
Very cool.
Hello, this guy still needs a bunch of shots.
A lot of HP.
I thought someone was just gonna snipe me.
I thought my laser pointer was an enemy laser pointer for a second.
Man, this place is huge.
Good.
Another wand.
Thank you.
I shall take it.
Formation.
Okay.
Very low cast delay on it.
Spells per cast four.
So that's pretty much useless.
The cast delay, I guess, because that's not going to come in use.
It's the recharge time that's going to be dominating here.
I wonder if you could somehow do that.
I don't want to call it exploit, but you know when we did the, when we sort of bypassed the recharge time by wrapping the whole thing around.
So it just kept looping.
We did that with one wand.
I forgot how we did it, but we did it.
I think we used a scatter actually for that.
But maybe there is a way.
Anyway, I'm gonna take this real quick and shoot it.
But, oh, that's cool.
The way that just did that.
Yeah.
I've been up here.
Wait, is that a frozen enemy?
Look at that.
Looks like a frozen ghostbuster.
The hell?
That's not just me, right?
That looked exactly like a frozen ghostbuster.
Okay.
Where am I even going?
Let's not go this way.
Go to the dark areas here.
Oh.
Come on.
I can't believe I've done this.
You know the smart thing about the laser pointers?
You can really pinpoint when you want to do this sort of stuff.
That's so good.
All right, let's go back.
Where we came from.
I want to go all the way to the left.
Isn't this the place where there was that really dark area?
Kind of want to go in there again.
Uh, what is that sound?
I'm scared.
Hold on.
Let me try this.
If I shoot this off, will I fall with it?
What?
It doesn't break off?
I thought this whole formation would break off.
That would be cool.
There's only some materials, it seems, that does this.
Others are sort of not doing it.
Oh shit.
Oh my god, this guy shoots quick.
There we go.
Crazy how they explode in such a violent manner.
I see gold.
Damn it.
That was a bit too close.
What's happening here?
That's a trap.
There's people in here too.
Amazing.
What's up guys?
Wait, is this link to the... hold on.
I'm scared.
Let me see here.
Can I
get in there?
Is this link somehow?
I'm scared.
What the hell is that?
Giant firebolt.
72 explosion on that?
Brother.
That seems nuts.
Let's try it.
Oh, that looks cool.
What?
Dude, imagine finding unlimited casts and using this.
Maybe I don't want the black hole in.
You There's an enemy down there.
Oh wait, was that just my laser pointer?
Am I being really dumb?
There's an enemy.
Dude, let me try and... Sir, do you like this?
Oh, did it even affect him?
What the heck?
Did he die?
Oh, there's something.
What the hell is that?
Oh, it's a... Oh.
Oh, I see.
He had a wand.
What is this now?
What the hell is that?
Spiral arc?
That projectile flies in a spiraling pattern.
Why is that good?
Pentagon.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Give me money.
There's a lot of it.
Oh, I'm taking a lot of damage.
I have been up there, but I've not been down... Have I been here?
I think I have been here.
Yeah.
I have not been in here, though.
This whole area is one of the best so far.
I just love the atmosphere of this place.
Also, Heezy base is awesome.
Oh, missile?
Summon missile?
Oh, wait.
I can't.
Oh, I can.
Okay.
I thought I was doomed.
Explosive bounce.
What's this?
Orbiting arc?
What sounds most intriguing?
I think this one does.
We got a summon missile.
Let's get rid of that one.
I don't like that.
Yoink!
Well, that means we got to find some more money before we move on.
Cool.
Found a little shop just in the middle of nowhere.
Not bad at all.
Ah!
There's the... Oh!
Hello!
What is this?
Volcanic sand.
Bam.
See ya.
Come on.
Give me that money.
I actually need the money.
Ah, shit.
That's too late.
Look at that!
He's totally frozen.
That is totally a ghostbuster.
I should use this some more.
Oh, this is where I came from.
Yeah, let me use this.
Oh, it's so much better actually.
Ah, let me use this real quick.
Blip blip.
Heel up.
Back we go.
What do we have over here?
Ambrosia.
I didn't quite remember what that was.
What the fuck is that?
Oh!
Fuck, I'm blind.
I didn't even see you.
What the hell?
Blip blip.
Jesus!
Rip... Ambrosia?
Whatever.
In fact, hold on.
What does it do again?
It feels strange strength in your body.
It's a defense up, I guess, right?
A missile!
Okay.
That's just what it says.
A missile with three exclamation marks.
Okay.
Oh, you know what?
I should probably go up again and heal.
We lost some HP in that encounter.
What was that?
Was it in here?
We could heal with this one, right?
No, that's what... that was the black hole one.
How was that wand I just found?
Ah, here it is.
There you go.
Full HP.
Cool!
Rip!
Definitely need some more money before we go through that.
Also, I gotta go to the left, because that's where the dark place was last time.
That's where I'm gonna go.
In fact, I can cut my way in there down there.
Let me go around.
What a huge mountain of snow.
Cut that snowman.
There we go.
Oh!
Didn't see you there.
I'm poisoned.
Let's wait for this.
What the hell's going on here?
Oh!
Nice!
I love the way they break open and gold just falls out.
Another wand down there.
Oh!
Cool!
Nothing.
Oh, wait!
What the hell's going on down here?
That was risky!
What I just did.
What if I encountered, like, a massive enemy?
Haha!
Actually kind of... Fuck you!
Money!
Cool!
Sick!
Oh, shit!
Get me out of here!
Okay, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I thought I was drowning.
Phew!
Haha!
That would have been a way to go, huh?
Imagine that.
Go up here.
Sick!
Ah, damn it!
I had one job.
Not to get hit by that.
Okay, we've been there.
The hell happened here?
Oh!
Look at the way this guy is vibrating!
What if I kick it?
Bup!
Hahaha!
Oh, shit!
Oh, my god!
Okay!
There's two of them!
I don't know why I'm surprised that happened when I kicked it.
All that money belongs to me now.
Very cool.
Remember that guy?
So, we've been here, I believe.
Everything's revealed.
I haven't been here.
500 gold?
Not bad.
Wait, okay.
I'm playing a little careless right now.
I'm not gonna lie.
This is what I... I admit that.
I admit that.
I lost a lot of HP for no reason recently, but that's fine because I have a bunch of ones I can heal with.
So, let me actually go do that.
Thank you.
I believe there were some to the east.
Uh, not here, down here.
Uh, this one I already, I think, used all of it.
But there's one to the right of this, somewhere.
I'm not mistaken.
This is very efficient, the way I'm traveling here.
Someone over here.
That's the one!
Heal me!
That's it.
I emptied that one.
There were some more over here.
There's one.
Let's see what this does before we fire it.
It shoots some kind of bullshit.
Cool.
Oh, shoot!
Right, okay, so it can... I think it's shot.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
Okay, heal up.
Maximum health.
That's all we needed.
Huh, I'm cured.
I'm tempted to take this with me because of the spells on it.
You know what?
Do that.
I want both of these because look at all the crazy spells on there.
There's also this one.
What does this one have?
Electric charge.
That's right.
I need to start thinking about what I want to bring with me.
Because I have many good options here.
Yeah, let's fuck you up.
Why can I not?
Wake up!
Wait, really?
It's a fake!
Boo!
Wow.
So some of them are fake, huh?
Looks like there's a maximum range on the teleport.
Like, it will teleport me somewhere halfway if I don't hit anything in time.
I'm gonna get through here.
I think it's time.
Nice.
You... What?
What did I do?
I have angered the gods.
Okay.
Is there anything good here?
Oh, shit.
Oh, what the fuck?
Oh, what's happening?
Huh?
Holy... What's happening?
What did I do?
We're leaving!
Grandpa...
Telekinetic powers.
Leave!
Is he after me?
The fuck's going on?
He died.
He died in the explosion.
Uh... No, it disappears!
Wait a minute.
Is that a wand?
I want to try and grab that.
What the fuck just happened, bro?
Uh, shit, man.
I didn't get to do anything here.
Does this destroy things?
Oh, it sure does.
Holy fuck!
I don't know what's happening, but it's awesome.
Can I... Can I go back and do things, please?
How did I anger the gods?
And what does that mean?
The fuck?
Okay.
Seems everything's fine now, at least.
I can buy this, I guess.
But do I want to buy that?
Oh, actually, 0.03... Oh, it's shuffle.
What is that first one?
I mean, I gotta use my money anyway, right?
Let's see what it is.
Formation behind your back.
Cast two spells, one ahead of you and one behind the caster.
Okay.
Weird.
But I don't want it.
I mean, I don't have much of a choice here.
This is what I've got, you know?
Hello, dude.
I guess we're just moving on like this.
That's a bit unfortunate, but it is what it is.
I have no idea what just happened, but that's actually kind of exciting.
Now, this place is nuts.
There's a lot of enemies in this place.
Here we go.
I've won already.
A magic bolt with timer.
Let's remember there's a heal in the start.
Oh, there's a heart!
Fuck yeah.
I'm going to use the ticket in there.
Wait, that doesn't explode on that.
Maybe I can go around.
Exquisite me.
Oh, that thing is nuts.
Come here.
Oh, you have a lot of HP.
Wow.
Wait, there's an enemy there.
Where did he come from?
What the hell?
How did I not lose any HP?
That's impressive.
I feel like I did lose a bunch, but apparently I didn't.
Come on.
Kick it.
Kick.
What?
Oh!
Oh, fuck man.
That scared me.
Give me a fright.
Fuck you.
I was so focused on this, I didn't even notice what was going on.
It's okay.
Wow, that won't let me in there.
How the fuck do I get in?
Oh wait, is it open?
Oh shit.
Don't stand in that.
What the hell am I going to get in there?
Can I cut?
Ah, I can cut.
Okay.
Perfect.
Why didn't I think about this?
Let's leak some of this.
Leak it.
Oh wait, it doesn't work there.
It does.
Get it out.
But look, the water reacts.
It's making it all water.
Yeah.
Cool.
And now we can heal a bit.
Let's see what this does before we shoot it.
Magical bolt with time.
What's it?
Magical bolt, huh?
Pretty neat.
I like the way that looks and feels.
Not bad at all.
In fact,
how fast does this shoot?
13.
Oh, hello.
That is insane.
That's an insane want.
Hello.
That's okay.
I'm taking this with me.
Fuck the other one.
That is amazing.
What happened here?
What?
Wait, what?
I'm back here now.
What the fuck happened here?
I must have triggered something when I went in here.
That dug all this somehow.
And for some reason, that angered the gods.
Whatever that means, right?
I mean, the fucking god came out, but he wasn't much of a god, was he?
He died from some debris falling on his head.
I'm going to keep exploring here now, man.
I wasn't done.
That's awesome.
I mean, I was done, but now I want to keep exploring.
Like what the fuck?
Look all this, all of this as well.
It's all nuts.
Look at that now.
What's that up there?
Oh, it's just ice.
Oh wait, I've been here.
I have ducked this hole.
I want to find a dark place.
I'm pretty sure that was in the snowy depths.
And there's a wand here as well.
Let me get to that.
That is an insane wand.
I don't... Okay, I think I do understand.
It's shooting a giant firebolt and then it's shooting three.
Makes sense.
Yeah, makes a lot of sense, actually.
There we go.
It's explained.
Um, no.
How about... Actually, let me see the stats on that.
That's an absurdly low cast delight, I gotta say.
But it shoots five spells at once and that's a little nuts.
But maybe nuts is exactly what we need, you know?
Let's get in here.
That means the next one is going to shoot three.
I'm going to save that for a big enemy.
Or a big wall.
One or the other.
I just broke that by crashing into it.
Look.
Awesome little detail.
There's the party up there, it seems.
Fireball thrower.
That's a fun one.
I had that on my glowing lance in one of my first very good runs.
And it carried me quite a lot.
Let me fuck these guys up.
Shit!
I almost fucked myself up.
Yeah, they had a bad day just now.
That's fantastic.
Hell yeah.
Okay, I've been up here.
What do we have over here?
What?
Are you invisible?
You're not, okay.
Holy crap!
This guy is nuts.
Yeah, he couldn't control it.
He died from it.
Power overwhelming.
Oh, it's my wand!
We're back!
But wait, it's shuffling.
That's scary.
I mean, why does that shoot it so far?
Usually it explodes much closer, no?
Oh, that's my boy right there.
That is my boy.
But it's... Okay, so look at the wand now.
You see the electric effect on it.
I think that's what happened when I died that one time.
Like, it simply has an electric effect on it right now, similar to how the fire wand always has like a fire effect on it.
It's always there.
So I put this in water and I electrocuted myself.
That's what happened.
Um, so I kind of want to keep this because I want these lightning bolts with me.
But I'm not going to use it.
So I want to replace my... Ah, man.
I want to replace my first wand.
But maybe that's crazy because it has a really nice spell on it.
I do want to keep this as well though.
It's a tough one.
Maybe I can live without this, you know?
Also, I don't have the explosion immunity.
It's fine.
I can live without that and I definitely want to play around with that wand too.
So this is going to do 13 damage per shot.
I think it's still less than this one.
But if I can add the damage plus on it and make it scatter and shit, that would be amazing.
If we... Ah, but then we need multiple of course, but...
Oh god, that's one of these guys.
Fucking weird-ass enemy.
You know what?
This wand over here is pretty good for this type of enemy.
Let me just pick it up for this specific purpose.
We're going to go hunting.
Let's just boop him a little bit.
Man, this spell is the tits.
I'll change my mind.
I'm going to keep it.
Yeah, I'm keeping.
It's a bit risky to play with, but it's the best.
It's so good.
And I will not equip it if I'm near water.
No way, Jose.
Let me also use this one instead here.
Gold for me.
Thank you.
What the fuck?
It's prickly.
Oh.
Oh, plus 40.
Oh, that's not that great.
But it's nice for healing.
I could use it to heal, I guess.
What the hell is in here?
That could have been bad.
I'm going to use this on him.
Are you okay, sir?
Nice.
It's a great wand.
And I think we're back to where we were before.
Yep.
Cool.
Another.
Wait, that's not a wand.
That's a berserkium.
Oh, what the fuck is that?
Okay.
Awesome.
That's a new enemy.
Cool how his jaw broke open.
And oh, this is the dark place.
We're here.
We made it.
The magical temple.
That was the name.
I don't have any light, do I?
I don't.
Imagine the all-seeing eye here.
Oh, man.
It's a horror game now.
Shit.
Oh, interesting spell he has there.
Let me fuck this guy up.
Man, thank God they're revealed, huh?
From a distance.
That means there's a guy over here as well.
Yeah, he's right in there.
Uh, who are you, sir?
Am I hitting you?
Shit.
Ow.
He's taking pot shots at me.
Did I hit him?
Dude, where are you?
Ah, motherfucker.
He's killing me slowly with a spoon.
There you are.
Come here.
Yeah, that's it, boy.
Oh, he has a lot of HP.
Fuck you.
That was the most painful thing ever.
I could cut my way in here, but why would I do that, actually?
On second thought, that's a terrible idea.
Wait, what's this?
Oh, never mind.
Ah, scared.
What the fuck is that?
What?
That's a wand.
Whoa!
Drilling shot?
Glue ball?
Plasma cutter?
Thunder charge?
The fuck?
I'm taking it.
That's way too much shit to experiment with there.
I don't know if I should be shooting it, though.
Hello.
Nice.
700 gold now.
What is... is that an enemy?
It's moving.
Let me take care of these guys first.
I hit him.
I was just about to shoot the new wand on accident there.
What was that?
I hit something just now and I don't know what it is.
Ow.
Fuck off.
You wanna dance?
Come here.
Yeah, you like that?
Oh, that's my wand.
Run!
Come on, come to me, come to me, come to me.
I can't see this guy.
That's the crazy thing.
Come on.
Come on, pussy.
Ah, reveal.
Reveal.
There you are.
What the hell is that?
Uh-oh.
One of these guys?
Not too bad.
Money.
Okay, he's right down.
Oh, he's shooting that thing?
Oh, my good.
I can do that too, buddy.
This is nuts.
How are you not dead?
Oh, shit.
Okay, I think I have to shoot the new wand I have.
So, what's it gonna do?
It's gonna shuffle.
Oh, no.
Fuck it.
Let's just shuffle it.
Ah, that's risky shit.
I'm gonna shoot it.
Wait, why is it?
Oh, never mind.
Okay, let's find some non-watery area just in case.
Okay.
That did nothing.
There we go.
Maximum heal.
Perfect.
I got him.
So, there's still a guy below me, I believe.
Did he die?
Oh, he died.
Nice.
Oh, he used mine.
No, wait.
What?
No, no, no, no.
This is my wand.
Where did the guy go who shot the purple shit?
Sir?
Where art thou?
What the fuck is this?
Let's just reveal it.
Uh-huh.
That's the entrance.
Wait.
What just happened there?
Oh, is that?
You gain neutral kinetic, dude.
Oh, what?
No way.
Wait, what's this?
Diamond?
Do I want that?
Wait.
Is that increasing my money?
No, it's not.
Okay.
Okay, that's awesome.
I can telekinetically move.
I completely forgot I had this because I was in a hurry when that happened.
Shit was popping off!
I almost died just now.
This is the motherfucker.
This is the guy.
Oh, man.
How is he not dead?
I hit him so much.
I gotta be kidding me.
Holy fuck.
Oh, not that.
I hit him straight.
I hit him straight there.
I got him.
I fucking got him.
Shit.
Do I get to use this wand, though?
Where'd the wand go?
It's gone.
Okay, I gotta go back and heal.
There's no way we're continuing on like this.
With this low HP.
No, no, no.
Not today, sir.
Let's do some healing here.
Now, where did we have a wand?
There.
Let's shoot this motherfucker.
Huh?
Wait, what?
Someone's a sport pot that I... Really?
Oh, damn.
Okay.
That's dangerous shit.
Don't fuck with that.
Wow, this requires a lot of recharge.
Just heal me up.
All right.
Let's just find another one to heal with.
That was pretty fun, though.
Could be nice to add as a sort of...
on a trigger for some other spell.
You know, if you shoot into an enclosed space and just have it hit a bunch of enemies.
That'll be fun.
Uh, this one I've already used a bunch, so that's not it.
Wait, where are all the wands?
It's not... I mean, I haven't been here yet.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm playing way too careless, but then again, we found a wand.
Ah, sure.
Not bad.
So where are the other wands?
There we go.
Oh, this one's going to be a little scary, though.
Fireball thrower.
Yeah.
Oh, it's a modifier, so it's gonna... Oh, it's shuffling.
That's scary.
Let's find an open space and do it.
Oh, oh, oh, holy crap.
Whoa.
Jesus.
The fuck?
All right.
Well, we did the healing.
It's over.
We don't have to do that one again.
What a crazy wand.
Damn.
I didn't expect it to be that nuts.
But okay.
Okay.
All right.
You know what?
I gotta end it here, man.
I am actually dying.
I need to eat right now.
I can definitely exit.
I'm gonna... Oh, save and quit.
Yeah, because I can click continue in the main menu.
So we're gonna be pausing this run.
I need to go save and quit.
Then we have some singing bowls.
Nice.
Dude, this is the run.
Guys, it's happening.
Next time I'm gonna get so far, especially because usually when you play this game for a long period of time, you tend to get a little careless.
You know what I mean?
But next time I'm gonna start fresh and be so far in the run.
It's either gonna be amazing or a total disaster where I forget what my wands do and I blow myself up.
It's one of those two.
But I'm leaning towards the first one more.
It's gonna be great.
I love the hymns fam.
I love the way it dances.
So I found this hymns on...
I just googled hymns pretty much.
And it was the first result.
So pretty nice.
You're gonna forget everything?
No, I'm not.
Watch.
I'm gonna remember everything.
It's gonna be incredible.
How you guys doing, man?
What are you guys doing this weekend?
I want to know.
So it's Friday, right?
You have any plans?
You will remember.
He promises.
I will have a good meal.
I'm actually gonna have Swedish meatball dish.
Or Svetsk-Pursarat, as we call it in Danish.
I don't know if that's the real thing they eat in Sweden.
I think it's a Danish made-up thing.
You're gonna play Neuter and Elden Ring.
Man, that sounds like a gaming session.
Two very difficult games, right?
I like it.
I love it.
Finally in holidays, we'll just sleep away.
Hmm, okay.
No plans, Hyve?
Not gonna celebrate your birthday?
That's weird.
Svetsk-Pursarat.
Yep, exactly.
You plan to solve a puzzle in Baba is You?
I've heard that's a difficult puzzle game.
It's on my list, too.
People have suggested it to me a bunch.
My plan is Elden Ring until my fingers are sore.
Oh, right, because the DLC, right?
That's
what it is.
Yeah, me neither, man.
The thing about Elden Ring is it's a big game.
And now that there's also a DLC, it's an even bigger game.
And I don't want to be in that situation where I started, and I'm going to have a bunch of real life obligations scattered in between.
So I'm going to wait with this game until I have a moment in my life where I can play it a lot.
You know?
Like really focus on it a lot.
So I don't know when that will be, but hopefully soon.
I don't want it to be too scattered.
I'm going to be way too scattered-brained on it otherwise, because I want to do theory and lore, theorizing about the lore and all that.
That's one of the best parts about playing FromSoft games.
Everyone have a good weekend?
You too, Cosmic Whale.
The DLC is hard for- I heard people complaining about the DLC being too hard.
That's all I know about it.
I just heard a bunch of- I saw a bunch of headlines, you know?
People were whining about it.
I think that's hilarious.
I'm just imagining Miyazaki sitting there grinning.
I fucking got him.
Honestly, I've played Rainworld.
I'm ready for anything.
Even this game doesn't feel as hard as Rainworld.
But maybe it will be later.
I don't know how far I am in Noita yet.
But I feel like I'm not that far, based on how many spells I've yet to discover and enemies to discover.
That's like the only way to measure things I have, right?
It's the progress page.
You're gonna have a good weekend?
Gonna be reading a lot?
Maybe rewatch my favorite- What is your favorite movie, Hive?
Tell me.
You've been playing through it a bit, and there's definitely a lot of Miyazaki moments.
Lovely.
So Poison Swamp confirmed them.
The Ritual.
Wait, what is that one?
The Ritual?
Ha!
I have not seen this one.
A group of old college friends reunite for a trip to the most dangerous country in Europe, Sweden.
Wait, what?
Is it a- Wait a minute.
Oh, it's not a- Okay, yeah, it's a movie.
Maybe.
That sounds hilarious.
I mean, it sounds accurate so far.
Okay, I'm gonna check out The Ritual, I think.
Maybe I'll watch it this weekend.
Anyway, I'm gonna raid another Neuter streamer.
Let's find one.
Let's see here, same category.
Who should we raid?
Let's see here.
There's a guy called Let's Suffer Together.
I mean, there's a bunch.
Let's try that.
I'm gonna go, guys.
I need to eat some food.
I'm gonna send you over to someone called Let's Suffer Together.
He's also playing Neuter right now.